<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Oracle SOA Suite on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>/fmw-kubernetes/20.3.3/soa-domains/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Oracle SOA Suite on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 16:43:45 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/fmw-kubernetes/20.3.3/soa-domains/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/20.3.3/soa-domains/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 11:25:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/20.3.3/soa-domains/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Review the latest changes and known issues for Oracle SOA Suite on Kubernetes.
Recent changes    Date Version Introduces backward incompatibilities Change     October 3, 2020 20.3.3 no Certified Oracle WebLogic Kubernetes operator version 3.0.1. Kubernetes 1.14.8+, 1.15.7+, 1.16.0+, 1.17.0+, and 1.18.0+ support. Flannel is the only supported CNI in this release. SSL enabling for the Administration Server and Managed Servers is supported. Only Oracle SOA Suite 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uninstall</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/20.3.3/soa-domains/cleanup-domain-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/20.3.3/soa-domains/cleanup-domain-setup/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to clean up the Oracle SOA Suite domain setup.
Remove the domain   Remove the domain&amp;rsquo;s ingress (for example, Traefik ingress) using Helm:
$ helm uninstall soa-domain-ingress -n sample-domain1-ns For example:
$ helm uninstall soainfra-traefik -n soans   Remove the domain resources by using the sample delete-weblogic-domain-resources.sh script present at ${WORKDIR}/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/kubernetes/samples/scripts/delete-domain:
$ cd ${WORKDIR}/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/kubernetes/samples/scripts/delete-domain $ ./delete-weblogic-domain-resources.sh -d sample-domain1 For example:
$ cd ${WORKDIR}/weblogic-kubernetes-operator/kubernetes/samples/scripts/delete-domain $ ./delete-weblogic-domain-resources.sh -d soainfra   Use kubectl to confirm that the server pods and domain resource are deleted:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frequently Asked Questions</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/20.3.3/soa-domains/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/20.3.3/soa-domains/faq/</guid>
      <description>Overriding tuning parameters is not supported using configuration overrides The Oracle WebLogic Server Kubernetes operator enables you to override some of the domain configuration using configuration overrides (also called situational configuration). See supported overrides. Overriding the tuning parameters such as MaxMessageSize and PAYLOAD, for Oracle SOA Suite domains is not supported using the configuration overrides feature. However, you can override them using the following steps:
  Specify the new value using the environment variable K8S_REFCONF_OVERRIDES in serverPod.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>