<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>/fmw-kubernetes/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 06:46:23 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/fmw-kubernetes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>a. Using Traefik Loadbalancer</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/wcsites-domains/manage-wcsites-domains/loadbalancer-traefik-setup-for-wcsites-domain-setup-on-k8s/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/wcsites-domains/manage-wcsites-domains/loadbalancer-traefik-setup-for-wcsites-domain-setup-on-k8s/</guid>
      <description>Setting Up Loadbalancer Traefik for the WebCenter Sites Domain on K8S The Oracle WebLogic Server Kubernetes Operator supports three load balancers: Traefik, Voyager, and Apache. Follow these steps to set up Traefik as a loadbalancer for the WebCenter Sites domain:
 Install the Traefik Load Balancer Configure Traefik to Manage Ingresses Create an Ingress for the Domain Verify that You can Access the Domain URL  Install the Traefik Load Balancer   Use helm to install the Traefik load balancer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>b. Using Voyager Loadbalancer</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/wcsites-domains/manage-wcsites-domains/loadbalancer-voyager-setup-for-wcsites-domain-setup-on-k8s/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/wcsites-domains/manage-wcsites-domains/loadbalancer-voyager-setup-for-wcsites-domain-setup-on-k8s/</guid>
      <description>Setting Up Loadbalancer Voyager for the WebCenter Sites Domain on K8S The Oracle WebLogic Server Kubernetes Operator supports three load balancers: Traefik, Voyager, and Apache. Follow these steps to set up Voyager as a loadbalancer for the WebCenter Sites domain:
 Install the Voyager Load Balancer Configure Voyager to Manage Ingresses Verify that You can Access the Domain URL  Install the Voyager Load Balancer See the official installation document and follow step 1 and 2 here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>c. ELK Integration for Logs</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/wcsites-domains/manage-wcsites-domains/elasticsearch-integration-with-wls-operator-and-wls-server-logs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/wcsites-domains/manage-wcsites-domains/elasticsearch-integration-with-wls-operator-and-wls-server-logs/</guid>
      <description>1. Integrate Elasticsearch to WebLogic Kubernetes Operator For reference information, see Elasticsearch integration for the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator.
To enable elasticsearch integration, you must edit file kubernetes/charts/weblogic-operator/values.yaml before deploying the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator.
# elkIntegrationEnabled specifies whether or not ELK integration is enabled. elkIntegrationEnabled: true # logStashImage specifies the docker image containing logstash. # This parameter is ignored if &#39;elkIntegrationEnabled&#39; is false. logStashImage: &amp;quot;logstash:6.6.0&amp;quot; # elasticSearchHost specifies the hostname of where Elasticsearch is running.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>d. Publish logs to Elasticsearch</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/wcsites-domains/manage-wcsites-domains/weblogic-logging-exporter-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/wcsites-domains/manage-wcsites-domains/weblogic-logging-exporter-setup/</guid>
      <description>The WebLogic Logging Exporter adds a log event handler to WebLogic Server. WebLogic Server logs can be pushed to Elasticsearch in Kubernetes directly by using the Elasticsearch REST API. For more details, see to the WebLogic Logging Exporter project.
This sample shows you how to publish WebLogic Server logs to Elasticsearch and view them in Kibana. For publishing operator logs, see this sample.
Prerequisites This document assumes that you have already set up Elasticsearch and Kibana for logs collection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>e. Monitor a WebCenter Sites domain</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/wcsites-domains/manage-wcsites-domains/weblogic-monitoring-exporter-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/wcsites-domains/manage-wcsites-domains/weblogic-monitoring-exporter-setup/</guid>
      <description>You can monitor a WebCenter Sites domain using Prometheus and Grafana by exporting the metrics from the domain instance using the WebLogic Monitoring Exporter. This sample shows you how to set up the WebLogic Monitoring Exporter to push the data to Prometheus.
Prerequisites This document assumes that the Prometheus Operator is deployed on the Kubernetes cluster. If it is not already deployed, follow the steps below for deploying the Prometheus Operator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/wcsites-domains/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/wcsites-domains/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Recent changes    Date Version Introduces backward incompatibilities Change     2020-03-18 2.4.0 No Starting with Oracle WebCenter Sites 12.2.1.4.0 support with WebLogic Kubernetes Operator 2.4.0    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>