<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Configure an Ingress for an OAM domain on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>/fmw-kubernetes/20.4.1/oam/configure-ingress/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Configure an Ingress for an OAM domain on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/fmw-kubernetes/20.4.1/oam/configure-ingress/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>a. Using an Ingress with NGINX</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/20.4.1/oam/configure-ingress/ingress-nginx-setup-for-oam-domain-setup-on-k8s/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/20.4.1/oam/configure-ingress/ingress-nginx-setup-for-oam-domain-setup-on-k8s/</guid>
      <description>Setting up an ingress for NGINX for the OAM Domain The instructions below explain how to set up NGINX as an ingress for the OAM domain with SSL termination.
Note: All the steps below should be performed on the master node.
 Generate a SSL Certificate Install NGINX Create an Ingress for the Domain Verify that You can Access the Domain URL  Generate a SSL Certificate   Generate a private key and certificate signing request (CSR) using a tool of your choice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>b. Using an Ingress with Voyager</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/20.4.1/oam/configure-ingress/ingress-voyager-setup-for-oam-domain-setup-on-k8s/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/20.4.1/oam/configure-ingress/ingress-voyager-setup-for-oam-domain-setup-on-k8s/</guid>
      <description>Setting Up an Ingress for Voyager for the OAM Domain on K8S The instructions below explain how to set up Voyager as an Ingress for the OAM domain with SSL termination.
Note: All the steps below should be performed on the master node.
 Generate a SSL Certificate Install Voyager Create an Ingress for the Domain Verify that You can Access the Domain URL  Generate a SSL Certificate   Generate a private key and certificate signing request (CSR) using a tool of your choice.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>