<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Deploy composite applications on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/deploying-composites/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Deploy composite applications on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 06:46:23 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/fmw-kubernetes/22.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/deploying-composites/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploy using JDeveloper</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/deploying-composites/supportjdev/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/deploying-composites/supportjdev/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to deploy Oracle SOA Suite and Oracle Service Bus composite applications from Oracle JDeveloper (running outside the Kubernetes network) to an Oracle SOA Suite instance in the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator environment.
Use JDeveloper for development and test environments only. For a production environment, you should deploy using Application Control and WLST methods.
 Deploy Oracle SOA Suite and Oracle Service Bus composite applications to Oracle SOA Suite from JDeveloper To deploy Oracle SOA Suite and Oracle Service Bus composite applications from Oracle JDeveloper, the Administration Server must be configured to expose a T3 channel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploy using Maven and Ant</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/deploying-composites/deploy-using-maven-ant/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/deploying-composites/deploy-using-maven-ant/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to deploy Oracle SOA Suite and Oracle Service Bus composite applications using the Maven and Ant based approach in an Oracle SOA Suite in WebLogic Kubernetes Operator environment.
Before deploying composite applications, we need to create a Kubernetes pod in the same cluster where the Oracle SOA Suite domain is running, so that composite applications can be deployed using the internal Kubernetes Service for the Administration Server URL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploy using composites in a persistent volume or image</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/deploying-composites/deploy-artifacts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 12:04:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/deploying-composites/deploy-artifacts/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to deploy Oracle SOA Suite and Oracle Service Bus composite applications artifacts in a Kubernetes persistent volume or in an image to an Oracle SOA Suite environment deployed using a WebLogic Kubernetes Operator.
The deployment methods described in Deploy using JDeveloper and Deploy using Maven and Ant are manual processes. If you have the deployment artifacts (archives) already built, then you can package them either into a Kubernetes persistent volume or in an image and use this automated process to deploy the artifacts to an Oracle SOA Suite domain.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>