<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 06:46:23 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Topology</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/edg-guide/topology/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/edg-guide/topology/</guid>
      <description>Assumptions The most relevant assumptions for the Oracle SOA Suite Kubernetes Enterprise Deployment Guide (EDG) topology are related to the database and web tiers. Typical on-premises production systems keep their high end database (such as RAC, RAC+DG, Exadata, Autonomous Database) out of the Kubernetes cluster and manage that tier separately. This implies that the database runs separately from the Kubernetes cluster hosting the application tier. The database provisioning and configuration process is out of the scope of the Oracle SOA Suite Kubernetes setup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 11:25:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Review the latest changes and known issues for Oracle SOA Suite on Kubernetes.
Recent changes    Date Version Change     August 31, 2022 22.3.2 Supports Oracle SOA Suite 12.2.1.4 domains deployment using July 2022 PSU and known bug fixes. Enterprise Deployment Guide as preview release. Oracle SOA Suite 12.2.1.4 Docker image for this release can be downloaded from My Oracle Support (MOS patch 34410491).   May 31, 2022 22.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploy using JDeveloper</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/adminguide/deploying-composites/supportjdev/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/adminguide/deploying-composites/supportjdev/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to deploy Oracle SOA Suite and Oracle Service Bus composite applications from Oracle JDeveloper (running outside the Kubernetes network) to an Oracle SOA Suite instance in the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator environment.
Use JDeveloper for development and test environments only. For a production environment, you should deploy using Application Control and WLST methods.
 Deploy Oracle SOA Suite and Oracle Service Bus composite applications to Oracle SOA Suite from JDeveloper To deploy Oracle SOA Suite and Oracle Service Bus composite applications from Oracle JDeveloper, the Administration Server must be configured to expose a T3 channel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Domain resource sizing</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/appendix/soa-cluster-sizing-info/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/appendix/soa-cluster-sizing-info/</guid>
      <description>Oracle SOA cluster sizing recommendations    Oracle SOA Normal Usage Moderate Usage High Usage     Administration Server No of CPU core(s) : 1, Memory : 4GB No of CPU core(s) : 1, Memory : 4GB No of CPU core(s) : 1, Memory : 4GB   Number of Managed Servers 2 2 4   Configurations per Managed Server No of CPU core(s) : 2, Memory : 16GB No of CPU core(s) : 4, Memory : 16GB No of CPU core(s) : 6, Memory : 16-32GB   PV Storage Minimum 250GB Minimum 250GB Minimum 500GB    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Patch an image</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/patch_and_upgrade/patch-an-image/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/patch_and_upgrade/patch-an-image/</guid>
      <description>Oracle releases Oracle SOA Suite images regularly with the latest bundle and recommended interim patches in My Oracle Support (MOS). However, if you need to create images with new bundle and interim patches, you can build these images using the WebLogic Image Tool.
If you have access to the Oracle SOA Suite patches, you can patch an existing Oracle SOA Suite image with a bundle patch and interim patches. Oracle recommends that you use the WebLogic Image Tool to patch the Oracle SOA Suite image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traefik</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/adminguide/configure-load-balancer/traefik/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/adminguide/configure-load-balancer/traefik/</guid>
      <description>This section provides information about how to install and configure the ingress-based Traefik load balancer (version 2.2.1 or later for production deployments) to load balance Oracle SOA Suite domain clusters. You can configure Traefik for non-SSL, SSL termination, and end-to-end SSL access of the application URL.
Follow these steps to set up Traefik as a load balancer for an Oracle SOA Suite domain in a Kubernetes cluster:
 Install the Traefik (ingress-based) load balancer Create an Ingress for the domain Verify domain application URL access Uninstall the Traefik ingress Uninstall Traefik  Install the Traefik (ingress-based) load balancer   Use Helm to install the Traefik (ingress-based) load balancer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup steps</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/edg-guide/setup-edg/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/edg-guide/setup-edg/</guid>
      <description>This section provides recommended steps to set up Oracle SOA Suite enterprise deployment on Kubernetes to eliminate single points of failure and to provide high availability.
 Set up your Kubernetes cluster Prepare the environment  Configure firewalls and network Load Oracle SOA Suite images on all the worker nodes Enable a shared storage location for the persistent volume   Create a database and the appropriate database services Install and configure Oracle HTTP Server in the DMZ Configure a front-end load balancer Apply operating system changes for Coherence Deploy WebLogic Kubernetes Operator and Oracle SOA Suite Configure redundant persistent volume Configure the required priority for mounts Set front-end addresses Enable FAN for GridLink data sources Configure ASM Configure coredns allocation Adjust server&amp;rsquo;s pods Liveness Probe  Set up your Kubernetes cluster Refer to the official Kubernetes documentation to set up a production-grade Kubernetes cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick start deployment on-premise</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/appendix/quickstart-deployment-on-prem/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/appendix/quickstart-deployment-on-prem/</guid>
      <description>Use this Quick Start to create an Oracle SOA Suite domain deployment in a Kubernetes cluster (on-premise environments) with the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator. Note that this walkthrough is for demonstration purposes only, not for use in production. These instructions assume that you are already familiar with Kubernetes. If you need more detailed instructions, refer to the Install Guide.
Hardware requirements The Linux kernel supported for deploying and running Oracle SOA Suite domains with the operator is Oracle Linux 7 (UL6+) and Red Hat Enterprise Linux 7 (UL3+ only with standalone Kubernetes).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploy using Maven and Ant</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/adminguide/deploying-composites/deploy-using-maven-ant/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/adminguide/deploying-composites/deploy-using-maven-ant/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to deploy Oracle SOA Suite and Oracle Service Bus composite applications using the Maven and Ant based approach in an Oracle SOA Suite in WebLogic Kubernetes Operator environment.
Before deploying composite applications, we need to create a Kubernetes pod in the same cluster where the Oracle SOA Suite domain is running, so that composite applications can be deployed using the internal Kubernetes Service for the Administration Server URL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enable additional URL access</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/adminguide/enable-additional-url-access/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/adminguide/enable-additional-url-access/</guid>
      <description>This section provides information about how to extend an existing ingress (Non-SSL and SSL termination) to enable additional application URL access for Oracle SOA Suite domains.
The ingress per domain created in the steps in Set up a load balancer exposes the application paths defined in template YAML files present at ${WORKDIR}/charts/ingress-per-domain/templates/.
To extend an existing ingress with additional application URL access:
  Update the template YAML file at ${WORKDIR}/charts/ingress-per-domain/templates/ to define additional path rules.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NGINX</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/adminguide/configure-load-balancer/nginx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/adminguide/configure-load-balancer/nginx/</guid>
      <description>This section provides information about how to install and configure the ingress-based NGINX load balancer to load balance Oracle SOA Suite domain clusters. You can configure NGINX for non-SSL, SSL termination, and end-to-end SSL access of the application URL.
Follow these steps to set up NGINX as a load balancer for an Oracle SOA Suite domain in a Kubernetes cluster:
See the official installation document for prerequisites.
 Install the NGINX load balancer for non-SSL and SSL termination configuration Generate secret for SSL access Install NGINX load balancer for end-to-end SSL configuration Configure NGINX to manage ingresses Verify domain application URL access Uninstall NGINX ingress Uninstall NGINX  To get repository information, enter the following Helm commands:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade an operator release</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/patch_and_upgrade/upgrade-operator-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/patch_and_upgrade/upgrade-operator-release/</guid>
      <description>To upgrade the WebLogic Kubernetes operator, use the helm upgrade command with new Helm chart and operator image. See the steps here to pull the operator image and set up the Oracle SOA Suite repository that contains the operator chart. To upgrade the operator run the following command:
$ cd ${WORKDIR} $ helm upgrade \ --reuse-values \ --set image=oracle/weblogic-kubernetes-operator:3.4.2 \ --namespace weblogic-operator-namespace \ --wait \ weblogic-kubernetes-operator \ charts/weblogic-operator  Note: When the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator is upgraded from release version 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploy using composites in a persistent volume or image</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/adminguide/deploying-composites/deploy-artifacts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 12:04:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/adminguide/deploying-composites/deploy-artifacts/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to deploy Oracle SOA Suite and Oracle Service Bus composite applications artifacts in a Kubernetes persistent volume or in an image to an Oracle SOA Suite environment deployed using a WebLogic Kubernetes Operator.
The deployment methods described in Deploy using JDeveloper and Deploy using Maven and Ant are manual processes. If you have the deployment artifacts (archives) already built, then you can package them either into a Kubernetes persistent volume or in an image and use this automated process to deploy the artifacts to an Oracle SOA Suite domain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache web tier</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/adminguide/configure-load-balancer/apache/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/adminguide/configure-load-balancer/apache/</guid>
      <description>This section provides information about how to install and configure the Apache web tier to load balance Oracle SOA Suite domain clusters. You can configure Apache web tier for non-SSL and SSL termination access of the application URL.
Follow these steps to set up the Apache web tier as a load balancer for an Oracle SOA Suite domain in a Kubernetes cluster:
 Build the Apache web tier image Create the Apache plugin configuration file Prepare the certificate and private key Install the Apache web tier Helm chart Verify domain application URL access Uninstall Apache web tier  Build the Apache web tier image Refer to the sample, to build the Apache web tier Docker image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configure SSL certificates</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/adminguide/configuring-custom-ssl-certificates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/adminguide/configuring-custom-ssl-certificates/</guid>
      <description>Secure Socket Layer (SSL) provides a secured communication for data sent over unsecured networks. In an SSL termination scenario, you can configure SSL between the client browser and the load balancer in your Oracle SOA Suite instance to ensure that applications are accessed securely. In an SSL end-to-end scenario, an Oracle SOA Suite domain is configured to use a self-signed SSL certificate that was generated during domain creation. Clients will typically receive a message indicating that the signing CA for the certificate is unknown and not trusted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security hardening</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/appendix/docker-k8s-hardening/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/appendix/docker-k8s-hardening/</guid>
      <description>Securing a Kubernetes cluster involves hardening on multiple fronts - securing the API servers, etcd, nodes, container images, container run-time, and the cluster network. Apply principles of defense in depth, principle of least privilege, and minimize the attack surface. Use security tools such as Kube-Bench to verify the cluster&amp;rsquo;s security posture. Since Kubernetes is evolving rapidly refer to Kubernetes Security Overview for the latest information on securing a Kubernetes cluster. Also ensure the deployed Docker containers follow the Docker Security guidance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade a Kubernetes cluster</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/patch_and_upgrade/upgrade-k8s-cluster/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/patch_and_upgrade/upgrade-k8s-cluster/</guid>
      <description>These instructions describe how to upgrade a Kubernetes cluster created using kubeadm on which an Oracle SOA Suite domain is deployed. A rolling upgrade approach is used to upgrade nodes (master and worker) of the Kubernetes cluster.
It is expected that there will be a down time during the upgrade of the Kubernetes cluster as the nodes need to be drained as part of the upgrade process.
 Prerequisites  Review Prerequisites and ensure that your Kubernetes cluster is ready for upgrade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitor a domain and publish logs</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/adminguide/monitoring-soa-domains/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/adminguide/monitoring-soa-domains/</guid>
      <description>After the Oracle SOA Suite domain is set up, you can:
 Monitor the Oracle SOA Suite instance using Prometheus and Grafana Publish WebLogic Server logs into Elasticsearch Publish SOA server diagnostics logs into Elasticsearch  Monitor the Oracle SOA Suite instance using Prometheus and Grafana Using the WebLogic Monitoring Exporter you can scrape runtime information from a running Oracle SOA Suite instance and monitor them using Prometheus and Grafana.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expose the T3/T3S protocol</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/adminguide/enablingt3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/adminguide/enablingt3/</guid>
      <description>Oracle strongly recommends that you do not expose non-HTTPS traffic (T3/T3s/LDAP/IIOP/IIOPs) outside of the external firewall. You can control this access using a combination of network channels and firewalls.
 You can create T3/T3S channels and the corresponding Kubernetes service to expose the T3/T3S protocol for the Administration Server and Managed Servers in an Oracle SOA Suite domain.
The WebLogic Kubernetes Operator provides an option to expose a T3 channel for the Administration Server using the exposeAdminT3Channel setting during domain creation, then the matching T3 service can be used to connect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uninstall</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/cleanup-domain-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/cleanup-domain-setup/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to clean up the Oracle SOA Suite domain setup.
Remove the domain   Remove the domain&amp;rsquo;s ingress (for example, Traefik ingress) using Helm:
$ helm uninstall soa-domain-ingress -n sample-domain1-ns For example:
$ helm uninstall soainfra-traefik -n soans   Remove the domain resources by using the sample delete-weblogic-domain-resources.sh script present at ${WORKDIR}/delete-domain:
$ cd ${WORKDIR}/delete-domain $ ./delete-weblogic-domain-resources.sh -d sample-domain1 For example:
$ cd ${WORKDIR}/delete-domain $ ./delete-weblogic-domain-resources.sh -d soainfra   Use kubectl to confirm that the server pods and domain resource are deleted:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Persist adapter customizations</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/adminguide/persisting-soa-adapters-customizations/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/adminguide/persisting-soa-adapters-customizations/</guid>
      <description>The lifetime for any customization done in a file on a server pod is up to the lifetime of that pod. The changes are not persisted once the pod goes down or is restarted.
For example, the following configuration updates DbAdapter.rar to create a new connection instance and creates data source CoffeeShop on the Administration Console for the same with jdbc/CoffeeShopDS.
File location: /u01/oracle/soa/soa/connectors/DbAdapter.rar
&amp;lt;connection-instance&amp;gt; &amp;lt;jndi-name&amp;gt;eis/DB/CoffeeShop&amp;lt;/jndi-name&amp;gt; &amp;lt;connection-properties&amp;gt; &amp;lt;properties&amp;gt; &amp;lt;property&amp;gt; &amp;lt;name&amp;gt;XADataSourceName&amp;lt;/name&amp;gt; &amp;lt;value&amp;gt;jdbc/CoffeeShopDS&amp;lt;/value&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/property&amp;gt; &amp;lt;property&amp;gt; &amp;lt;name&amp;gt;DataSourceName&amp;lt;/name&amp;gt; &amp;lt;value&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/value&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/property&amp;gt; &amp;lt;property&amp;gt; &amp;lt;name&amp;gt;PlatformClassName&amp;lt;/name&amp;gt; &amp;lt;value&amp;gt;org.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frequently Asked Questions</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/faq/</guid>
      <description>Overriding tuning parameters is not supported using configuration overrides The WebLogic Kubernetes Operator enables you to override some of the domain configuration using configuration overrides (also called situational configuration). See supported overrides. Overriding the tuning parameters such as MaxMessageSize and PAYLOAD, for Oracle SOA Suite domains is not supported using the configuration overrides feature. However, you can override them using the following steps:
  Specify the new value using the environment variable K8S_REFCONF_OVERRIDES in serverPod.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perform WLST operations</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/adminguide/performing-wlst-operations/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.3.2/soa-domains/adminguide/performing-wlst-operations/</guid>
      <description>You can use the WebLogic Scripting Tool (WLST) to manage a domain running in a Kubernetes cluster. Some of the many ways to do this are provided here.
If the Administration Server was configured to expose a T3 channel using exposeAdminT3Channel when creating the domain, refer to Use WLST.
If you do not want to expose additional ports and perform WLST administration operations using the existing Kubernetes services created by the WebLogic Server Kubernetes operator, then follow this documentation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>