<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Upgrade and Patch  on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.1.1/wcsites-domains/patch-and-upgrade/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Upgrade and Patch  on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 15:44:42 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/fmw-kubernetes/21.1.1/wcsites-domains/patch-and-upgrade/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Patch a Oracle WebCenter Sites product Docker image</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.1.1/wcsites-domains/patch-and-upgrade/patch-an-image/patch-wcsites-product-image/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.1.1/wcsites-domains/patch-and-upgrade/patch-an-image/patch-wcsites-product-image/</guid>
      <description>These instructions describe how to upgrade a new release of Oracle WebCenter Sites product Docker image in a running Oracle WebCenter Sites Kubernetes environment. A rolling upgrade approach is used to upgrade managed server pods of the domain.
It is expecting a Zero down time as a rolling upgrade approach is used.
 Prerequisites  Make sure Oracle WebCenter Sites domain is created and all the admin and managed pods are up and running.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade an operator release</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.1.1/wcsites-domains/patch-and-upgrade/upgrade-operator-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.1.1/wcsites-domains/patch-and-upgrade/upgrade-operator-release/</guid>
      <description>These instructions apply to upgrading operators within the 3.x release family as additional versions are released.
To upgrade the Kubernetes operator, use the helm upgrade command. When upgrading the operator, the helm upgrade command requires that you supply a new Helm chart and image. For example:
$ helm upgrade \ --reuse-values \ --set image=oracle/weblogic-kubernetes-operator:3.0.2 \ --namespace weblogic-operator-namespace \ --wait \ weblogic-operator \ kubernetes/charts/weblogic-operator </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade a Kubernetes cluster</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.1.1/wcsites-domains/patch-and-upgrade/upgrade-k8s-cluster/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.1.1/wcsites-domains/patch-and-upgrade/upgrade-k8s-cluster/</guid>
      <description>These instructions describe how to upgrade a Kubernetes cluster created using kubeadm on which an Oracle WebCenter Sites domain is deployed. A rolling upgrade approach is used to upgrade nodes (master and worker) of the Kubernetes cluster.
It is expected that there will be a down time during the upgrade of the Kubernetes cluster as the nodes need to be drained as part of the upgrade process.
 Prerequisites  Review Prerequisites and ensure that your Kubernetes cluster is ready for upgrade.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>