<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Manage OAM Domains on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oam/manage-oam-domains/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Manage OAM Domains on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oam/manage-oam-domains/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>a. Domain Life Cycle</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oam/manage-oam-domains/domain-lifecycle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oam/manage-oam-domains/domain-lifecycle/</guid>
      <description>As OAM domains use the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator, domain lifecyle operations are managed using the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator itself.
This document shows the basic operations for starting, stopping and scaling servers in the OAM domain.
For more detailed information refer to Domain Life Cycle in the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator documentation.
Do not use the WebLogic Server Administration Console or Oracle Enterprise Manager Console to start or stop servers.
 View existing OAM servers The default OAM deployment starts the Administration Server (AdminServer), two OAM Managed Servers (oam_server1 and oam_server2) and two OAM Policy Manager server (oam_policy_mgr1 and oam_policy_mgr2 ).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>b. WLST Administration Operations</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oam/manage-oam-domains/wlst-admin-operations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oam/manage-oam-domains/wlst-admin-operations/</guid>
      <description>To use WLST to administer the OAM domain, use the helper pod in the same Kubernetes cluster as the OAM Domain.
  Run the following command to start a bash shell in the helper pod:
$ kubectl exec -it helper -n &amp;lt;domain_namespace&amp;gt; -- /bin/bash For example:
$ kubectl exec -it helper -n oamns -- /bin/bash This will take you into a bash shell in the running helper pod:
[oracle@helper ~]$   Connect to WLST using the following command:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>c. Logging and Visualization</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oam/manage-oam-domains/logging-and-visualization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oam/manage-oam-domains/logging-and-visualization/</guid>
      <description>After the OAM domain is set up you can publish operator and WebLogic Server logs into Elasticsearch and interact with them in Kibana.
In Prepare your environment if you decided to use the Elasticsearch and Kibana by setting the parameter elkIntegrationEnabled to true, then the steps below must be followed to complete the setup.
If you did not set elkIntegrationEnabled to true and want to do so post configuration, run the following command from the $WORKDIR directory:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>d. Monitoring an OAM domain</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oam/manage-oam-domains/monitoring-oam-domains/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oam/manage-oam-domains/monitoring-oam-domains/</guid>
      <description>After the OAM domain is set up you can monitor the OAM instance using Prometheus and Grafana. See Monitoring a domain.
The WebLogic Monitoring Exporter uses the WLS RESTful Management API to scrape runtime information and then exports Prometheus-compatible metrics. It is deployed as a web application in a WebLogic Server (WLS) instance, version 12.2.1 or later, typically, in the instance from which you want to get metrics.
There are two ways to setup monitoring and you should choose one method or the other:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>e. Delete the OAM domain home</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oam/manage-oam-domains/delete-domain-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oam/manage-oam-domains/delete-domain-home/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes in production, but most likely in testing environments, you might want to remove the domain home that is generated using the create-domain.sh script.
  Run the following command to delete the domain:
$ cd $WORKDIR/kubernetes/delete-domain $ ./delete-weblogic-domain-resources.sh -d &amp;lt;domain_uid&amp;gt; For example:
$ cd $WORKDIR/kubernetes/delete-domain $ ./delete-weblogic-domain-resources.sh -d accessdomain   Drop the RCU schemas as follows:
$ kubectl exec -it helper -n &amp;lt;domain_namespace&amp;gt; -- /bin/bash [oracle@helper ~]$ [oracle@helper ~]$ export CONNECTION_STRING=&amp;lt;db_host.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>