<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Oracle Cloud Infrastructure on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.2/wcsites-domains/oracle-cloud/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Oracle Cloud Infrastructure on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 15:44:42 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.2/wcsites-domains/oracle-cloud/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparing an OKE environment</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.2/wcsites-domains/oracle-cloud/oke/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.2/wcsites-domains/oracle-cloud/oke/</guid>
      <description>Overview Create Public SSH Key to access all the Bastion/Worker nodes  Create SSH key using ssh-keygen on linux terminal.  Generating public/private rsa key pair. Your identification has been saved in &amp;lt;path&amp;gt;/id_rsa. Your public key has been saved in &amp;lt;path&amp;gt;/id_rsa.pub. The key fingerprint is: SHA256:xCi1gf1QFafbRwOM3WjUTgqEInwi6UklbuxbBeMzA6M demokey The key&amp;#39;s randomart image is: +---[RSA 2048]----+ | +++oo..++*++ | | ++==+==. oo=.+ | |Eo+o*+++o .o +o | | oo * .. o.... | | .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparing the Bastion host</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.2/wcsites-domains/oracle-cloud/bastion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.2/wcsites-domains/oracle-cloud/bastion/</guid>
      <description>STEP 1 : Create Public Security List Create Public Security List (bastion_public_sec_list) in same VCN as that of OKE Cluster for Bastion Node
 Ingress Rules as: (where 10.0.22.0/24 is the CIDR planned to be used for bastion subnet)  Egress as:   STEP 2 : Create Private Security List Create Private Security List (bastion_private_sec_list) in same VCN as that of OKE Cluster which will be added into Worker Node subnet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparing a file system</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.2/wcsites-domains/oracle-cloud/filesystem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.2/wcsites-domains/oracle-cloud/filesystem/</guid>
      <description>Create Filesystem and security list for FSS Note: Make sure you create the filesystem and security list in the OKE created VCN
 Login to OCI Console and go to File Storage and Click &amp;ldquo;File System&amp;rdquo;  Click &amp;ldquo;Create File System&amp;rdquo;  You can create File System and Mount Targets with the default values. But in case you want to rename the file System and mount targets, follow below steps. Note: Make Sure the Virtual Cloud Network in Mount Target refers to the one where your instances are created and you will be accessing this file system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating an OCIR</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.2/wcsites-domains/oracle-cloud/ocir/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.2/wcsites-domains/oracle-cloud/ocir/</guid>
      <description>Creation of OCIR Push all the required images to OCIR and use from OCIR. Follow the below steps before pushing the images to OCIR
Create an &amp;ldquo;Auth token&amp;rdquo; Create an &amp;ldquo;Auth token&amp;rdquo; which will be used as docker password to push/pull images from OCIR Login to Console and navigate to User Settings, which is in the drop down under your OCI username in the top nav  On User Details page, select &amp;ldquo;Auth Tokens&amp;rdquo; in the left nav and then Click the &amp;ldquo;Generate Token&amp;rdquo; button: Enter a Name and Click &amp;ldquo;Generate Token&amp;rdquo;  Token will get generated  Copy the generated token.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>