<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 06:46:23 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparing an OKE environment</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wccontent-domains/oracle-cloud/prepare-oke-environment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 16:43:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wccontent-domains/oracle-cloud/prepare-oke-environment/</guid>
      <description>Contents  Create Public SSH Key to access all the Bastion and Worker nodes Create a compartment for OKE Create Container Clusters (OKE) Create Bastion Node to access Cluster Setup OCI CLI to download kubeconfig and access OKE Cluster  Create Public SSH Key to access all the Bastion and Worker nodes Create SSH key using ssh-keygen on linux terminal to access (ssh) the Compute instances (worker/bastion) in OCI.
ssh-keygen -t rsa -N &amp;#34;&amp;#34; -b 2048 -C demokey -f id_rsa Create a compartment for OKE Within your tenancy, there must be a compartment to contain the necessary network resources (VCN, subnets, internet gateway, route table, security lists).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Domain resource sizing</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wccontent-domains/appendix/wcc-cluster-sizing-info/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wccontent-domains/appendix/wcc-cluster-sizing-info/</guid>
      <description>Oracle WebCenter Content cluster sizing recommendations    Oracle WCC Normal Usage Moderate Usage High Usage     Administration Server No of CPU core(s) : 1, Memory : 4GB No of CPU core(s) : 1, Memory : 4GB No of CPU core(s) : 1, Memory : 4GB   Number of Managed Servers 2 3 5   Configurations per Managed Server No of CPU core(s) : 2, Memory : 16GB No of CPU core(s) : 4, Memory : 16GB No of CPU core(s) : 6, Memory : 16-32GB   PV Storage Minimum 250GB Minimum 250GB Minimum 500GB    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Patch a Oracle WebCenter Sites product Docker image</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wcsites-domains/patch-and-upgrade/patch-an-image/patch-wcsites-product-image/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wcsites-domains/patch-and-upgrade/patch-an-image/patch-wcsites-product-image/</guid>
      <description>These instructions describe how to upgrade a new release of Oracle WebCenter Sites product Docker image in a running Oracle WebCenter Sites Kubernetes environment. A rolling upgrade approach is used to upgrade managed server pods of the domain.
It is expecting a Zero down time as a rolling upgrade approach is used.
 Prerequisites  Make sure Oracle WebCenter Sites domain is created and all the admin and managed pods are up and running.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparing a file system</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wccontent-domains/oracle-cloud/filesystem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wccontent-domains/oracle-cloud/filesystem/</guid>
      <description>Create Filesystem and security list for FSS  Note: Make sure you create the filesystem and security list in the OKE created VCN
   Login to OCI Console and go to Storage and Click File System   Click Create File System   You can create File System and Mount Targets with the default values. But in case you want to rename the file System and mount targets, follow below steps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparing an OKE environment</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wcsites-domains/oracle-cloud/oke/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wcsites-domains/oracle-cloud/oke/</guid>
      <description>Overview Create Public SSH Key to access all the Bastion/Worker nodes  Create SSH key using ssh-keygen on linux terminal.  Generating public/private rsa key pair. Your identification has been saved in &amp;lt;path&amp;gt;/id_rsa. Your public key has been saved in &amp;lt;path&amp;gt;/id_rsa.pub. The key fingerprint is: SHA256:xCi1gf1QFafbRwOM3WjUTgqEInwi6UklbuxbBeMzA6M demokey The key&amp;#39;s randomart image is: +---[RSA 2048]----+ | +++oo..++*++ | | ++==+==. oo=.+ | |Eo+o*+++o .o +o | | oo * .. o.... | | .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparing OCIR</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wccontent-domains/oracle-cloud/ocir/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wccontent-domains/oracle-cloud/ocir/</guid>
      <description>Publish images to OCIR Push all the required images to OCIR and subsequently use from there. Follow the below steps for pushing the images to OCIR
Create an &amp;ldquo;Auth token&amp;rdquo; Create an &amp;ldquo;Auth token&amp;rdquo; which will be used as docker password to push and pull images from OCIR. Login to OCI Console and navigate to User Settings, which is in the drop down under your OCI user-profile, located at the top-right corner of the OCI console page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wcsites-domains/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 11:25:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wcsites-domains/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Review the latest changes and known issues for Oracle WebCenter Sites on Kubernetes.
Recent changes    Date Version Introduces backward incompatibilities Change     Dec 10, 2021 21.4.3 no Certified Oracle WebLogic Kubernetes Operator version 3.3.0. Kubernetes 1.16.0+, 1.17.0+, and 1.18.0+ support. Flannel is the only supported CNI in this release. Only Webcenter Sites 12.2.1.4 is supported.   Jan 15, 2021 21.1.1 no Certified Oracle WebLogic Kubernetes Operator version 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Domain resource sizing</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wcsites-domains/appendix/wcsites-cluster-sizing-info/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wcsites-domains/appendix/wcsites-cluster-sizing-info/</guid>
      <description>Oracle WebCenter Sites cluster sizing recommendations    Oracle WebCenter Sites Normal Usage Moderate Usage High Usage     Administration Server No of CPU core(s) : 1, Memory : 4GB No of CPU core(s) : 1, Memory : 4GB No of CPU core(s) : 1, Memory : 4GB   Managed Server No of Servers : 2, No of CPU core(s) : 2, Memory : 16GB No of Servers : 2, No of CPU core(s) : 4, Memory : 16GB No of Servers : 3, No of CPU core(s) : 6, Memory : 16-32GB   PV Storage Minimum 250GB Minimum 250GB Minimum 500GB    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traefik</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wcsites-domains/adminguide/configure-load-balancer/traefik/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wcsites-domains/adminguide/configure-load-balancer/traefik/</guid>
      <description>This section provides information about how to install and configure the ingress-based Traefik load balancer (version 2.2.1 or later for production deployments) to load balance Oracle WebCenter Sites domain clusters. You can configure Traefik for access of the application URL.
Follow these steps to set up Traefik as a load balancer for an Oracle WebCenter Sites domain in a Kubernetes cluster:
Setting Up Loadbalancer Traefik for the WebCenter Sites Domain on K8S Follow these steps to set up Traefik as a loadbalancer for the Oracle WebCenter Sites domain:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Patch an image</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wccontent-domains/patch_and_upgrade/patch-an-image/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wccontent-domains/patch_and_upgrade/patch-an-image/</guid>
      <description>Oracle aims to release Oracle WebCenter Content images regularly with latest bundle and recommended interim patches in My Oracle Support (MOS). However, if there is a need to create images with new bundle and interim patches, you can build these images using WebLogic Image Tool.
If you have access to the Oracle WebCenter Content patches, you can patch an existing Oracle WebCenter Content image with a bundle patch and interim patches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wccontent-domains/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wccontent-domains/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Review the latest changes for Oracle WebCenter Content on Kubernetes.
Recent changes    Date Version Change     December 7, 2021 21.4.3 Supports Oracle WebCenter Content 12.2.1.4 domains deployment using April 2021 PSU and known bug fixes - certified for Oracle WebLogic Kubernetes Operator version 3.2.5. Oracle WebCenter Content 12.2.1.4 container image for this release can be downloaded from My Oracle Support (MOS patch 32822360).   June 16, 2021 21.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traefik</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wccontent-domains/adminguide/configure-load-balancer/traefik/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wccontent-domains/adminguide/configure-load-balancer/traefik/</guid>
      <description>This section provides information about how to install and configure the ingress-based Traefik load balancer (version 2.2.1 or later for production deployments) to load balance Oracle WebCenter Content domain clusters. You can configure Traefik for non-SSL, SSL termination and end-to-end SSL access of the application URL.
Follow these steps to set up Traefik as a load balancer for an Oracle WebCenter Content	domain in a Kubernetes cluster:
  Non-SSL and SSL termination</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traefik</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wccontent-domains/oracle-cloud/configure-load-balancer/traefik/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wccontent-domains/oracle-cloud/configure-load-balancer/traefik/</guid>
      <description>This section provides information about how to install and configure the ingress-based Traefik load balancer (version 2.2.8 or later for production deployments) to load balance Oracle WebCenter Content domain clusters.
Follow these steps to set up Traefik as a load balancer for an Oracle WebCenter Content	domain in a Kubernetes cluster:
Contents  Install the Traefik (ingress-based) load balancer Configure Traefik to manage ingresses Create an Ingress for the domain Verify domain application URL access Uninstall the Traefik ingress  Install the Traefik (ingress-based) load balancer   Use Helm to install the Traefik (ingress-based) load balancer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick start deployment guide</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wccontent-domains/appendix/quickstart-deployment-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wccontent-domains/appendix/quickstart-deployment-guide/</guid>
      <description>Use this Quick Start to create an Oracle WebCenter Content domain deployment in a Kubernetes cluster (on-premise environments) with WebLogic Kubernetes Operator. Note that this walkthrough is for demonstration purposes only, not for use in production. These instructions assume that you are already familiar with Kubernetes. If you need more detailed instructions, refer to the Install Guide.
Hardware requirements Supported Linux kernel for deploying and running Oracle WebCenter Content domain with the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator is Oracle Linux 7 (UL6+) and Red Hat Enterprise Linux 7 (UL3+ only with standalone Kubernetes).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NGINX</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wccontent-domains/adminguide/configure-load-balancer/nginx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wccontent-domains/adminguide/configure-load-balancer/nginx/</guid>
      <description>This section provides information about how to install and configure the ingress-based NGINX load balancer to load balance Oracle WebCenter Content domain clusters. You can configure NGINX for non-SSL, SSL termination, and end-to-end SSL access of the application URL.
Follow these steps to set up NGINX as a load balancer for an Oracle WebCenter Content domain in a Kubernetes cluster:
See the official installation document for prerequisites.
  Non-SSL and SSL termination</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick start deployment on-premise</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wcsites-domains/appendix/quickstart-deployment-on-prem/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wcsites-domains/appendix/quickstart-deployment-on-prem/</guid>
      <description>Use this Quick Start to create an Oracle WebCenter Sites domain deployment in a Kubernetes cluster (on-premise environments) with the Oracle WebLogic Server Kubernetes operator. Note that this walkthrough is for demonstration purposes only, not for use in production. These instructions assume that you are already familiar with Kubernetes. If you need more detailed instructions, refer to the Install Guide.
Hardware requirements Supported Linux kernel for deploying and running Oracle WebCenter Sites domains with the operator is Oracle Linux 7 UL6+ and Red Hat Enterprise Linux 7 (UL3+).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparing the Bastion host</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wcsites-domains/oracle-cloud/bastion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wcsites-domains/oracle-cloud/bastion/</guid>
      <description>STEP 1 : Create Public Security List Create Public Security List (bastion_public_sec_list) in same VCN as that of OKE Cluster for Bastion Node
 Ingress Rules as: (where 10.0.22.0/24 is the CIDR planned to be used for bastion subnet)  Egress as:   STEP 2 : Create Private Security List Create Private Security List (bastion_private_sec_list) in same VCN as that of OKE Cluster which will be added into Worker Node subnet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NGINX</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wcsites-domains/adminguide/configure-load-balancer/nginx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wcsites-domains/adminguide/configure-load-balancer/nginx/</guid>
      <description>This section provides information about how to install and configure the ingress-based NGINX load balancer to load balance Oracle WebCenter Sites domain clusters. You can configure NGINX for access of the application URL.
Follow these steps to set up NGINX as a load balancer for an Oracle WebCenter Sites domain in a Kubernetes cluster:
See the official installation document for prerequisites.
Add the Helm repos (if not added) Add following Helm repos</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade an operator release</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wcsites-domains/patch-and-upgrade/upgrade-operator-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wcsites-domains/patch-and-upgrade/upgrade-operator-release/</guid>
      <description>These instructions apply to upgrading operators within the 3.x release family as additional versions are released.
To upgrade the Kubernetes operator, use the helm upgrade command. When upgrading the operator, the helm upgrade command requires that you supply a new Helm chart and image. For example:
$ helm upgrade \ --reuse-values \ --set image=oracle/weblogic-kubernetes-operator:3.0.2 \ --namespace weblogic-operator-namespace \ --wait \ weblogic-operator \ kubernetes/charts/weblogic-operator </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitor an Oracle WebCenter Content domain</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wccontent-domains/adminguide/weblogic-monitoring-exporter-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wccontent-domains/adminguide/weblogic-monitoring-exporter-setup/</guid>
      <description>You can monitor a WebCenter Content domain using Prometheus and Grafana by exporting the metrics from the domain instance using the WebLogic Monitoring Exporter. This sample shows you how to set up the WebLogic Monitoring Exporter to push the data to Prometheus.
Prerequisites This document assumes that the Prometheus Operator is deployed on the Kubernetes cluster. If it is not already deployed, follow the steps below for deploying the Prometheus Operator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade an WebLogic Kubernetes Operator release</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wccontent-domains/patch_and_upgrade/upgrade-operator-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wccontent-domains/patch_and_upgrade/upgrade-operator-release/</guid>
      <description>These instructions apply to upgrading WebLogic Kubernetes Operators within the 3.x release family as additional versions are released.
To upgrade WebLogic Kubernetes Operator, use the helm upgrade command. Make sure that the weblogic-kubernetes-operator repository on your local machine is at the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator release to which you are upgrading. When upgrading the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator, the helm upgrade command requires that you supply a new Helm chart and image. For example:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security hardening</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wccontent-domains/appendix/docker-k8s-hardening/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wccontent-domains/appendix/docker-k8s-hardening/</guid>
      <description>Securing a Kubernetes cluster involves hardening on multiple fronts - securing the API servers, etcd, nodes, container images, container run-time, and the cluster network. Apply principles of defense in depth, principle of least privilege, and minimize the attack surface. Use security tools such as Kube-Bench to verify the cluster&amp;rsquo;s security posture. Since Kubernetes is evolving rapidly refer to Kubernetes Security Overview for the latest information on securing a Kubernetes cluster. Also ensure the deployed Docker containers follow the Docker Security guidance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elasticsearch integration for logs</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wccontent-domains/adminguide/elasticsearch-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 16:43:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wccontent-domains/adminguide/elasticsearch-integration/</guid>
      <description>1. Integrate Elasticsearch to WebLogic Kubernetes Operator For reference information, see Elasticsearch integration for the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator.
To enable elasticsearch integration, you must edit file kubernetes/charts/weblogic-operator/values.yaml before deploying the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator.
# elkIntegrationEnabled specifies whether or not ELK integration is enabled. elkIntegrationEnabled: true # logStashImage specifies the docker image containing logstash. # This parameter is ignored if &#39;elkIntegrationEnabled&#39; is false. logStashImage: &amp;quot;logstash:6.6.0&amp;quot; # elasticSearchHost specifies the hostname of where Elasticsearch is running.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparing a file system</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wcsites-domains/oracle-cloud/filesystem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wcsites-domains/oracle-cloud/filesystem/</guid>
      <description>Create Filesystem and security list for FSS Note: Make sure you create the filesystem and security list in the OKE created VCN
 Login to OCI Console and go to File Storage and Click &amp;ldquo;File System&amp;rdquo;  Click &amp;ldquo;Create File System&amp;rdquo;  You can create File System and Mount Targets with the default values. But in case you want to rename the file System and mount targets, follow below steps. Note: Make Sure the Virtual Cloud Network in Mount Target refers to the one where your instances are created and you will be accessing this file system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitor a domain and publish logs</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wcsites-domains/adminguide/monitoring-wcsites-domains/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wcsites-domains/adminguide/monitoring-wcsites-domains/</guid>
      <description>After the Oracle WebCenter Sites domain is set up, you can:
 Monitor the Oracle WebCenter Sites instance using Prometheus and Grafana Publish WebLogic Server logs into Elasticsearch  Monitor the Oracle WebCenter Sites instance using Prometheus and Grafana Using the WebLogic Monitoring Exporter you can scrape runtime information from a running Oracle WebCenter Sites instance and monitor them using Prometheus and Grafana.
Prerequisites This document assumes that the Prometheus Operator is deployed on the Kubernetes cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security hardening</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wcsites-domains/appendix/docker-k8s-hardening/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wcsites-domains/appendix/docker-k8s-hardening/</guid>
      <description>Securing a Kubernetes cluster involves hardening on multiple fronts - securing the API servers, etcd, nodes, container images, container run-time, and the cluster network. Apply principles of defense in depth, principle of least privilege, and minimize the attack surface. Use security tools such as Kube-Bench to verify the cluster&amp;rsquo;s security posture. Since Kubernetes is evolving rapidly refer to Kubernetes Security Overview for the latest information on securing a Kubernetes cluster. Also ensure the deployed Docker containers follow the Docker Security guidance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade a Kubernetes cluster</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wcsites-domains/patch-and-upgrade/upgrade-k8s-cluster/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wcsites-domains/patch-and-upgrade/upgrade-k8s-cluster/</guid>
      <description>These instructions describe how to upgrade a Kubernetes cluster created using kubeadm on which an Oracle WebCenter Sites domain is deployed. A rolling upgrade approach is used to upgrade nodes (master and worker) of the Kubernetes cluster.
It is expected that there will be a down time during the upgrade of the Kubernetes cluster as the nodes need to be drained as part of the upgrade process.
 Prerequisites  Review Prerequisites and ensure that your Kubernetes cluster is ready for upgrade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade a Kubernetes cluster</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wccontent-domains/patch_and_upgrade/upgrade-k8s-cluster/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wccontent-domains/patch_and_upgrade/upgrade-k8s-cluster/</guid>
      <description>These instructions describe how to upgrade a Kubernetes cluster created using kubeadm on which an Oracle WebCenter Content domain is deployed. A rolling upgrade approach is used to upgrade nodes (master and worker) of the Kubernetes cluster.
It is expected that there will be a down time during the upgrade of the Kubernetes cluster as the nodes need to be drained as part of the upgrade process.
 Prerequisites  Review Prerequisites and ensure that your Kubernetes cluster is ready for upgrade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publish logs to Elasticsearch</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wccontent-domains/adminguide/weblogic-logging-exporter-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 16:43:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wccontent-domains/adminguide/weblogic-logging-exporter-setup/</guid>
      <description>The WebLogic Logging Exporter adds a log event handler to WebLogic Server. WebLogic Server logs can be pushed to Elasticsearch in Kubernetes directly by using the Elasticsearch REST API. For more details, see to the WebLogic Logging Exporter project.
This sample shows you how to publish WebLogic Server logs to Elasticsearch and view them in Kibana. For publishing WebLogic Kubernetes Operator logs, see this sample.
Prerequisites This document assumes that you have already set up Elasticsearch and Kibana for logs collection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating an OCIR</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wcsites-domains/oracle-cloud/ocir/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wcsites-domains/oracle-cloud/ocir/</guid>
      <description>Creation of OCIR Push all the required images to OCIR and use from OCIR. Follow the below steps before pushing the images to OCIR
Create an &amp;ldquo;Auth token&amp;rdquo; Create an &amp;ldquo;Auth token&amp;rdquo; which will be used as docker password to push/pull images from OCIR Login to Console and navigate to User Settings, which is in the drop down under your OCI username in the top nav  On User Details page, select &amp;ldquo;Auth Tokens&amp;rdquo; in the left nav and then Click the &amp;ldquo;Generate Token&amp;rdquo; button: Enter a Name and Click &amp;ldquo;Generate Token&amp;rdquo;  Token will get generated  Copy the generated token.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elasticsearch integration for logs</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wcsites-domains/adminguide/elasticsearch-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wcsites-domains/adminguide/elasticsearch-integration/</guid>
      <description>1. Integrate Elasticsearch to WebLogic Kubernetes Operator For reference information, see Elasticsearch integration for the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator.
To enable elasticsearch integration, you must edit file kubernetes/charts/weblogic-operator/values.yaml before deploying the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator.
# elkIntegrationEnabled specifies whether or not ELK integration is enabled. elkIntegrationEnabled: true # logStashImage specifies the Docker image containing logstash. # This parameter is ignored if &#39;elkIntegrationEnabled&#39; is false. logStashImage: &amp;quot;logstash:6.6.0&amp;quot; # elasticSearchHost specifies the hostname of where Elasticsearch is running.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publish logs to Elasticsearch</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wcsites-domains/adminguide/weblogic-logging-exporter-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wcsites-domains/adminguide/weblogic-logging-exporter-setup/</guid>
      <description>The WebLogic Logging Exporter adds a log event handler to WebLogic Server. WebLogic Server logs can be pushed to Elasticsearch in Kubernetes directly by using the Elasticsearch REST API. For more details, see to the WebLogic Logging Exporter project.
This sample shows you how to publish WebLogic Server logs to Elasticsearch and view them in Kibana. For publishing operator logs, see this sample.
Prerequisites This document assumes that you have already set up Elasticsearch and Kibana for logs collection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache webtier</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wccontent-domains/adminguide/configure-load-balancer/apache/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wccontent-domains/adminguide/configure-load-balancer/apache/</guid>
      <description>This section provides information about how to install and configure Apache webtier to load balance Oracle WebCenter Content domain clusters. You can configure Apache webtier for non-SSL and SSL termination access of the application URL.
Follow these steps to set up Apache webtier as a load balancer for an Oracle WebCenter Content domain in a Kubernetes cluster:
 Build the Apache webtier image Create the Apache plugin configuration file Prepare the certificate and private key Install the Apache webtier Helm chart Verify domain application URL access Uninstall Apache webtier  Build the Apache webtier image Refer to the sample, to build the Apache webtier Docker image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publish logs to Elasticsearch Using Fluentd</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wccontent-domains/adminguide/logging-fluentd-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 16:43:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wccontent-domains/adminguide/logging-fluentd-setup/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This page describes to how to configure a WebLogic domain to use Fluentd to send log information to Elasticsearch. Here’s the general mechanism for how this works:
 fluentd runs as a separate container in the Administration Server and Managed Server pods The log files reside on a volume that is shared between the weblogic-server and fluentd containers fluentd tails the domain logs files and exports them to Elasticsearch A ConfigMap contains the filter and format rules for exporting log records.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uninstall</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wcsites-domains/cleanup-domain-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wcsites-domains/cleanup-domain-setup/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to clean up the Oracle WebCenter Sites domain setup.
Stop all Administration and Managed server pods First stop the all pods related to a domain. This can be done by patching domain &amp;ldquo;serverStartPolicy&amp;rdquo; to &amp;ldquo;NEVER&amp;rdquo;. Here is the sample command for the same.
$ kubectl patch domain wcsites-domain-name -n wcsites-namespace --type=&amp;#39;json&amp;#39; -p=&amp;#39;[{&amp;#34;op&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;replace&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;path&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;/spec/serverStartPolicy&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;value&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;NEVER&amp;#34; }]&amp;#39; For example:
$ kubectl patch domain wcsitesinfra -n wcsites-ns --type=&amp;#39;json&amp;#39; -p=&amp;#39;[{&amp;#34;op&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;replace&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;path&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;/spec/serverStartPolicy&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;value&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;NEVER&amp;#34; }]&amp;#39; Drop the RCU schemas $ cd work-dir-name/weblogic-kubernetes-operator $ kubectl apply -f kubernetes/create-wcsites-domain/output/weblogic-domains/wcsitesinfra/delete-domain-job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uninstall</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wccontent-domains/cleanup-domain-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wccontent-domains/cleanup-domain-setup/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to clean up the Oracle WebCenter Content domain setup.
Stop all Administration and Managed server pods First stop the all pods related to a domain. This can be done by patching domain &amp;ldquo;serverStartPolicy&amp;rdquo; to &amp;ldquo;NEVER&amp;rdquo;. Here is the sample command for the same.
$ kubectl patch domain wcc-domain-name -n wcc-namespace --type=&amp;#39;json&amp;#39; -p=&amp;#39;[{&amp;#34;op&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;replace&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;path&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;/spec/serverStartPolicy&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;value&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;NEVER&amp;#34; }]&amp;#39; For example:
kubectl patch domain wccinfra -n wccns --type=&amp;#39;json&amp;#39; -p=&amp;#39;[{&amp;#34;op&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;replace&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;path&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;/spec/serverStartPolicy&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;value&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;NEVER&amp;#34; }]&amp;#39; Remove the domain   Remove the domain&amp;rsquo;s ingress (for example, Traefik ingress) using Helm:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frequently Asked Questions</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wcsites-domains/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.3/wcsites-domains/faq/</guid>
      <description>Configure the external URL access for Oracle WebCenter Sites composite applications For Oracle WebCenter Sites composite applications to access the external URLs over the internet (if your cluster is behind a http proxy server), you must configure the following proxy parameters for Administration Server and Managed Server pods.
-Dhttp.proxyHost=www-your-proxy.com -Dhttp.proxyPort=proxy-port -Dhttps.proxyHost=www-your-proxy.com -Dhttps.proxyPort=proxy-port -Dhttp.nonProxyHosts=&amp;#34;localhost|wcsitesinfra-adminserver|wcsitesinfra-wcsites-server1|*.svc.cluster.local|*.your.domain.com|/var/run/docker.sock&amp;#34; To do this, edit the domain.yaml configuration file and append the proxy parameters to the spec.serverPod.env.JAVA_OPTIONS environment variable value.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>