<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Appendix on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.1.1/wcsites-domains/appendix/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Appendix on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 15:27:38 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/fmw-kubernetes/21.1.1/wcsites-domains/appendix/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Domain resource sizing</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.1.1/wcsites-domains/appendix/wcsites-cluster-sizing-info/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.1.1/wcsites-domains/appendix/wcsites-cluster-sizing-info/</guid>
      <description>Oracle WebCenter Sites cluster sizing recommendations    Oracle WebCenter Sites Normal Usage Moderate Usage High Usage     Administration Server No of CPU core(s) : 1, Memory : 4GB No of CPU core(s) : 1, Memory : 4GB No of CPU core(s) : 1, Memory : 4GB   Managed Server No of Servers : 2, No of CPU core(s) : 2, Memory : 16GB No of Servers : 2, No of CPU core(s) : 4, Memory : 16GB No of Servers : 3, No of CPU core(s) : 6, Memory : 16-32GB   PV Storage Minimum 250GB Minimum 250GB Minimum 500GB    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick start deployment on-premise</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.1.1/wcsites-domains/appendix/quickstart-deployment-on-prem/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.1.1/wcsites-domains/appendix/quickstart-deployment-on-prem/</guid>
      <description>Use this Quick Start to create an Oracle WebCenter Sites domain deployment in a Kubernetes cluster (on-premise environments) with the Oracle WebLogic Server Kubernetes operator. Note that this walkthrough is for demonstration purposes only, not for use in production. These instructions assume that you are already familiar with Kubernetes. If you need more detailed instructions, refer to the Install Guide.
Hardware requirements Supported Linux kernel for deploying and running Oracle WebCenter Sites domains with the operator is Oracle Linux 7 UL6+ and Red Hat Enterprise Linux 7 (UL3+).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security hardening</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.1.1/wcsites-domains/appendix/docker-k8s-hardening/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.1.1/wcsites-domains/appendix/docker-k8s-hardening/</guid>
      <description>Securing a Kubernetes cluster involves hardening on multiple fronts - securing the API servers, etcd, nodes, container images, container run-time, and the cluster network. Apply principles of defense in depth, principle of least privilege, and minimize the attack surface. Use security tools such as Kube-Bench to verify the cluster&amp;rsquo;s security posture. Since Kubernetes is evolving rapidly refer to Kubernetes Security Overview for the latest information on securing a Kubernetes cluster. Also ensure the deployed Docker containers follow the Docker Security guidance.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>