<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Patch and upgrade on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.1.3/wccontent-domains/patch_and_upgrade/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Patch and upgrade on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 16:43:45 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/fmw-kubernetes/22.1.3/wccontent-domains/patch_and_upgrade/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Patch an image</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.1.3/wccontent-domains/patch_and_upgrade/patch-an-image/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.1.3/wccontent-domains/patch_and_upgrade/patch-an-image/</guid>
      <description>Oracle aims to release Oracle WebCenter Content images regularly with latest bundle and recommended interim patches in My Oracle Support (MOS). However, if there is a need to create images with new bundle and interim patches, you can build these images using WebLogic Image Tool.
If you have access to the Oracle WebCenter Content patches, you can patch an existing Oracle WebCenter Content image with a bundle patch and interim patches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade an WebLogic Kubernetes Operator release</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.1.3/wccontent-domains/patch_and_upgrade/upgrade-operator-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.1.3/wccontent-domains/patch_and_upgrade/upgrade-operator-release/</guid>
      <description>These instructions apply to upgrading WebLogic Kubernetes Operators within the 3.x release family as additional versions are released.
To upgrade WebLogic Kubernetes Operator, use the helm upgrade command. Make sure that the weblogic-kubernetes-operator repository on your local machine is at the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator release to which you are upgrading. When upgrading the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator, the helm upgrade command requires that you supply a new Helm chart and image. For example:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade a Kubernetes cluster</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.1.3/wccontent-domains/patch_and_upgrade/upgrade-k8s-cluster/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.1.3/wccontent-domains/patch_and_upgrade/upgrade-k8s-cluster/</guid>
      <description>These instructions describe how to upgrade a Kubernetes cluster created using kubeadm on which an Oracle WebCenter Content domain is deployed. A rolling upgrade approach is used to upgrade nodes (master and worker) of the Kubernetes cluster.
It is expected that there will be a down time during the upgrade of the Kubernetes cluster as the nodes need to be drained as part of the upgrade process.
 Prerequisites  Review Prerequisites and ensure that your Kubernetes cluster is ready for upgrade.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>