<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Manage Oracle Internet Directory Containers on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.1/oid/manage-oid-containers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Manage Oracle Internet Directory Containers on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.1/oid/manage-oid-containers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>a) Scaling Up/Down OID Pods </title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.1/oid/manage-oid-containers/scaling-up-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.1/oid/manage-oid-containers/scaling-up-down/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This section describes how to increase or decrease the number of OID pods in the Kubernetes deployment.
View existing OID pods By default the oid helm chart deployment starts two pods: oidhost1 and oidhost2.
The number of pods started is determined by the replicaCount, which is set to 1 by default. A value of 1 starts the two pods above.
To scale up or down the number of OID pods, set replicaCount accordingly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>c) Monitoring an Oracle Internet Directory Instance</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.1/oid/manage-oid-containers/monitoring-oid-instance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.1/oid/manage-oid-containers/monitoring-oid-instance/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Install Prometheus and Grafana  Create a Kubernetes namespace Add Prometheus and Grafana Helm repositories Install the Prometheus operator View Prometheus and Grafana objects created Add the NodePort   Verify using Grafana GUI  Introduction After the Oracle Internet Directory instance (OID) is set up you can monitor it using Prometheus and Grafana.
Install Prometheus and Grafana Create a Kubernetes namespace   Create a Kubernetes namespace to provide a scope for Prometheus and Grafana objects such as pods and services that you create in the environment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>