<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Oracle Unified Directory Services Manager on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.1/oudsm/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Oracle Unified Directory Services Manager on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.1/oudsm/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.1/oudsm/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.1/oudsm/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Review the latest changes and known issues for Oracle Unified Directory Services Manager on Kubernetes.
Recent changes    Date Version Change     April, 2022 22.2.1 Updated for CRI-O support.   November 2021 21.4.2 Voyager ingress removed as no longer supported.   October 2021 21.4.1 A) References to supported Kubernetes, Helm and Docker versions removed and replaced with Support note reference. B) Namespace and domain names changed to be consistent with Enterprise Deployment Guide for Oracle Identity and Access Management in a Kubernetes Cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Patch and Upgrade</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.1/oudsm/patch-and-upgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.1/oudsm/patch-and-upgrade/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this section the Oracle Unified Directory Services Manager (OUDSM) deployment is updated with a new OUDSM container image.
Note: If you are not using Oracle Container Registry or your own container registry, then you must first load the new container image on all nodes in your Kubernetes cluster.
You can update the deployment with a new OUDSM container image using one of the following methods:
 Using a YAML file Using --set argument  Using a YAML file   Navigate to the $WORKDIR/kubernetes/helm directory:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>