<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Manage OAM Domains on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.4.1/oam/manage-oam-domains/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Manage OAM Domains on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/fmw-kubernetes/22.4.1/oam/manage-oam-domains/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>a. Domain Life Cycle</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.4.1/oam/manage-oam-domains/domain-lifecycle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.4.1/oam/manage-oam-domains/domain-lifecycle/</guid>
      <description>View existing OAM servers Starting/Scaling up OAM Managed servers Stopping/Scaling down OAM Managed servers Stopping and starting the Administration Server and Managed Servers Domain lifecycle sample scripts  As OAM domains use the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator, domain lifecyle operations are managed using the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator itself.
This document shows the basic operations for starting, stopping and scaling servers in the OAM domain.
For more detailed information refer to Domain Life Cycle in the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator documentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>b. WLST Administration Operations</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.4.1/oam/manage-oam-domains/wlst-admin-operations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.4.1/oam/manage-oam-domains/wlst-admin-operations/</guid>
      <description>To use WLST to administer the OAM domain, use the helper pod in the same Kubernetes cluster as the OAM Domain.
  Check to see if the helper pod exists by running:
$ kubectl get pods -n &amp;lt;domain_namespace&amp;gt; | grep helper For example:
$ kubectl get pods -n oamns | grep helper The output should look similar to the following:
helper 1/1 Running 0 26h If the helper pod doesn&amp;rsquo;t exist then see Step 1 in Prepare your environment  to create it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>c. Logging and Visualization</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.4.1/oam/manage-oam-domains/logging-and-visualization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.4.1/oam/manage-oam-domains/logging-and-visualization/</guid>
      <description>After the OAM domain is set up you can publish operator and WebLogic Server logs into Elasticsearch and interact with them in Kibana.
Install Elasticsearch stack and Kibana If you do not already have a centralized Elasticsearch (ELK) stack then you must configure this first. For details on how to configure the ELK stack, follow Installing Elasticsearch (ELK) Stack and Kibana
Create the logstash pod Variables used in this chapter In order to create the logstash pod, you must create several files.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>d. Monitoring an OAM domain</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.4.1/oam/manage-oam-domains/monitoring-oam-domains/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.4.1/oam/manage-oam-domains/monitoring-oam-domains/</guid>
      <description>After the OAM domain is set up you can monitor the OAM instance using Prometheus and Grafana. See Monitoring a domain.
The WebLogic Monitoring Exporter uses the WLS RESTful Management API to scrape runtime information and then exports Prometheus-compatible metrics. It is deployed as a web application in a WebLogic Server (WLS) instance, version 12.2.1 or later, typically, in the instance from which you want to get metrics.
There are two ways to setup monitoring and you should choose one method or the other:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>e. Delete the OAM domain home</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.4.1/oam/manage-oam-domains/delete-domain-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.4.1/oam/manage-oam-domains/delete-domain-home/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes in production, but most likely in testing environments, you might want to remove the domain home that is generated using the create-domain.sh script.
  Run the following command to delete the domain:
$ cd $WORKDIR/kubernetes/delete-domain $ ./delete-weblogic-domain-resources.sh -d &amp;lt;domain_uid&amp;gt; For example:
$ cd $WORKDIR/kubernetes/delete-domain $ ./delete-weblogic-domain-resources.sh -d accessdomain   Drop the RCU schemas as follows:
$ kubectl exec -it helper -n &amp;lt;domain_namespace&amp;gt; -- /bin/bash [oracle@helper ~]$ [oracle@helper ~]$ export CONNECTION_STRING=&amp;lt;db_host.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>