<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Enterprise Deployment Guide on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.4.2/soa-domains/edg-guide/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Enterprise Deployment Guide on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 15:44:42 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/fmw-kubernetes/22.4.2/soa-domains/edg-guide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Topology</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.4.2/soa-domains/edg-guide/topology/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.4.2/soa-domains/edg-guide/topology/</guid>
      <description>Assumptions The most relevant assumptions for the Oracle SOA Suite Kubernetes Enterprise Deployment Guide (EDG) topology are related to the database and web tiers. Typical on-premises production systems keep their high end database (such as RAC, RAC+DG, Exadata, Autonomous Database) out of the Kubernetes cluster and manage that tier separately. This implies that the database runs separately from the Kubernetes cluster hosting the application tier. The database provisioning and configuration process is out of the scope of the Oracle SOA Suite Kubernetes setup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup steps</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.4.2/soa-domains/edg-guide/setup-edg/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.4.2/soa-domains/edg-guide/setup-edg/</guid>
      <description>This section provides recommended steps to set up Oracle SOA Suite enterprise deployment on Kubernetes to eliminate single points of failure and to provide high availability.
 Set up your Kubernetes cluster Prepare the environment  Configure firewalls and network Load Oracle SOA Suite images on all the worker nodes Enable a shared storage location for the persistent volume   Create a database and the appropriate database services Install and configure Oracle HTTP Server in the DMZ Configure a front-end load balancer Create worker nodes Apply operating system changes for Coherence Deploy WebLogic Kubernetes Operator and Oracle SOA Suite Configure redundant persistent volume Configure the required priority for mounts Set front-end addresses Enable FAN for GridLink data sources Configure ASM Configure coredns allocation Adjust server&amp;rsquo;s pods Liveness Probe  Set up your Kubernetes cluster Prepare the environment for the Kubernetes control plane (Master nodes)   Create the L4/TCP listener for the load balancer (LBR).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>