<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Patch and upgrade on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>/fmw-kubernetes/20.3.3/soa-domains/patch_and_upgrade/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Patch and upgrade on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 15:27:38 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/fmw-kubernetes/20.3.3/soa-domains/patch_and_upgrade/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Patch an image</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/20.3.3/soa-domains/patch_and_upgrade/patch-an-image/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/20.3.3/soa-domains/patch_and_upgrade/patch-an-image/</guid>
      <description>Oracle releases Oracle SOA Suite images regularly with latest bundle and recommended interim patches in My Oracle Support (MOS). However, if there is a need to create images with new bundle and interim patches, you can build these images using WebLogic Image Tool.
If you have access to the Oracle SOA Suite patches, you can patch an existing Oracle SOA Suite image with a bundle patch and interim patches. It is recommended to use the WebLogic Image Tool to patch the Oracle SOA Suite image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade an operator release</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/20.3.3/soa-domains/patch_and_upgrade/upgrade-operator-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/20.3.3/soa-domains/patch_and_upgrade/upgrade-operator-release/</guid>
      <description>These instructions apply to upgrading operators within the 3.x release family as additional versions are released.
To upgrade the Kubernetes operator, use the helm upgrade command. When upgrading the operator, the helm upgrade command requires that you supply a new Helm chart and image. For example:
$ helm upgrade \ --reuse-values \ --set image=oracle/weblogic-kubernetes-operator:3.0.1 \ --namespace weblogic-operator-namespace \ --wait \ weblogic-operator \ kubernetes/charts/weblogic-operator </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade a Kubernetes cluster</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/20.3.3/soa-domains/patch_and_upgrade/upgrade-k8s-cluster/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/20.3.3/soa-domains/patch_and_upgrade/upgrade-k8s-cluster/</guid>
      <description>These instructions describe how to upgrade a Kubernetes cluster created using kubeadm on which an Oracle SOA Suite domain is deployed. A rolling upgrade approach is used to upgrade nodes (master and worker) of the Kubernetes cluster.
It is expected that there will be a down time during the upgrade of the Kubernetes cluster as the nodes need to be drained as part of the upgrade process.
 Prerequisites  Review Prerequisites and ensure that your Kubernetes cluster is ready for upgrade.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>