<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 06:46:23 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oam/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 11:25:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oam/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Review the latest changes and known issues for Oracle Access Management on Kubernetes.
Recent changes    Date Version Change     November, 2021 21.4.2 Supports Oracle Access Management domain deployment using WebLogic Kubernetes Operator 3.3.0. Voyager ingress removed as no longer supported.   October 2021 21.4.1 A) References to supported Kubernetes, Helm and Docker versions removed and replaced with Support note reference. B) Namespace and domain names changed to be consistent with Enterprise Deployment Guide for Oracle Identity and Access Management in a Kubernetes Cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oid/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 11:25:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oid/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Review the latest changes and known issues for Oracle Internet Directory on Kubernetes.
Recent changes    Date Version Change     October, 2021 21.4.1 Initial release of Oracle Identity Directory on Kubernetes.    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oig/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 11:25:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oig/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Review the latest changes and known issues for Oracle Identity Governance on Kubernetes.
Recent changes    Date Version Change     November, 2021 21.4.2 Supports Oracle Identity Governance domain deployment using WebLogic Kubernetes Operator 3.3.0. Voyager ingress removed as no longer supported.   October 2021 21.4.1 A) References to supported Kubernetes, Helm and Docker versions removed and replaced with Support note reference. B) Namespace and domain names changed to be consistent with Enterprise Deployment Guide for Oracle Identity and Access Management in a Kubernetes Cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oud/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 11:25:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oud/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Review the latest changes and known issues for Oracle Unified Directory on Kubernetes.
Recent changes    Date Version Change     November 2021 21.4.2 Voyager ingress removed as no longer supported.   October 2021 21.4.1 A) References to supported Kubernetes, Helm and Docker versions removed and replaced with Support note reference. B) Namespace and domain names changed to be consistent with Enterprise Deployment Guide for Oracle Identity and Access Management in a Kubernetes Cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oudsm/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 11:25:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oudsm/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Review the latest changes and known issues for Oracle Unified Directory Services Manager on Kubernetes.
Recent changes    Date Version Change     November 2021 21.4.2 Voyager ingress removed as no longer supported.   October 2021 21.4.1 A) References to supported Kubernetes, Helm and Docker versions removed and replaced with Support note reference. B) Namespace and domain names changed to be consistent with Enterprise Deployment Guide for Oracle Identity and Access Management in a Kubernetes Cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 11:25:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Review the latest changes and known issues for Oracle SOA Suite on Kubernetes.
Recent changes    Date Version Change     November 30, 2021 21.4.2 Supports Oracle SOA Suite 12.2.1.4 domains deployment using October 2021 PSU and known bug fixes. Oracle SOA Suite 12.2.1.4 Docker image for this release can be downloaded from My Oracle Support (MOS patch 33467899).   August 6, 2021 21.3.2 Supports Oracle SOA Suite 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploy using JDeveloper</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/deploying-composites/supportjdev/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/deploying-composites/supportjdev/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to deploy Oracle SOA Suite and Oracle Service Bus composite applications from Oracle JDeveloper (running outside the Kubernetes network) to an Oracle SOA Suite instance in the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator environment.
Use JDeveloper for development and test environments only. For a production environment, you should deploy using Application Control and WLST methods.
 Deploy Oracle SOA Suite and Oracle Service Bus composite applications to Oracle SOA Suite from JDeveloper To deploy Oracle SOA Suite and Oracle Service Bus composite applications from Oracle JDeveloper, the Administration Server must be configured to expose a T3 channel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Domain resource sizing</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/appendix/soa-cluster-sizing-info/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/appendix/soa-cluster-sizing-info/</guid>
      <description>Oracle SOA cluster sizing recommendations    Oracle SOA Normal Usage Moderate Usage High Usage     Administration Server No of CPU core(s) : 1, Memory : 4GB No of CPU core(s) : 1, Memory : 4GB No of CPU core(s) : 1, Memory : 4GB   Number of Managed Servers 2 2 4   Configurations per Managed Server No of CPU core(s) : 2, Memory : 16GB No of CPU core(s) : 4, Memory : 16GB No of CPU core(s) : 6, Memory : 16-32GB   PV Storage Minimum 250GB Minimum 250GB Minimum 500GB    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Patch an image</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/patch_and_upgrade/patch-an-image/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/patch_and_upgrade/patch-an-image/</guid>
      <description>Oracle releases Oracle SOA Suite images regularly with the latest bundle and recommended interim patches in My Oracle Support (MOS). However, if you need to create images with new bundle and interim patches, you can build these images using the WebLogic Image Tool.
If you have access to the Oracle SOA Suite patches, you can patch an existing Oracle SOA Suite image with a bundle patch and interim patches. Oracle recommends that you use the WebLogic Image Tool to patch the Oracle SOA Suite image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traefik</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/configure-load-balancer/traefik/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/configure-load-balancer/traefik/</guid>
      <description>This section provides information about how to install and configure the ingress-based Traefik load balancer (version 2.2.1 or later for production deployments) to load balance Oracle SOA Suite domain clusters. You can configure Traefik for non-SSL, SSL termination, and end-to-end SSL access of the application URL.
Follow these steps to set up Traefik as a load balancer for an Oracle SOA Suite domain in a Kubernetes cluster:
 Install the Traefik (ingress-based) load balancer Create an Ingress for the domain Verify domain application URL access Uninstall the Traefik ingress Uninstall Traefik  Install the Traefik (ingress-based) load balancer   Use Helm to install the Traefik (ingress-based) load balancer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>a. Using Design Console with NGINX(non-SSL)</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oig/configure-design-console/using-the-design-console-with-nginx-non-ssl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oig/configure-design-console/using-the-design-console-with-nginx-non-ssl/</guid>
      <description>Configure an NGINX ingress (non-SSL) to allow Design Console to connect to your Kubernetes cluster.
  Prerequisites
  Setup routing rules for the Design Console ingress
  Create the ingress
  Update the T3 channel
  Restart the OIG domain
  Design Console client
a. Using an on-premises installed Design Console
b. Using a container image for Design Console
  Login to the Design Console</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Domain life cycle</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oig/manage-oig-domains/domain-lifecycle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oig/manage-oig-domains/domain-lifecycle/</guid>
      <description>View existing OIG servers Starting/Scaling up OIG Managed servers Stopping/Scaling down OIG Managed servers Stopping and starting the Administration Server and Managed Servers  As OIG domains use the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator, domain lifecyle operations are managed using the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator itself.
This document shows the basic operations for starting, stopping and scaling servers in the OIG domain.
For more detailed information refer to Domain Life Cycle in the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator documentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick start deployment on-premise</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/appendix/quickstart-deployment-on-prem/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 15:27:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/appendix/quickstart-deployment-on-prem/</guid>
      <description>Use this Quick Start to create an Oracle SOA Suite domain deployment in a Kubernetes cluster (on-premise environments) with the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator. Note that this walkthrough is for demonstration purposes only, not for use in production. These instructions assume that you are already familiar with Kubernetes. If you need more detailed instructions, refer to the Install Guide.
Hardware requirements The Linux kernel supported for deploying and running Oracle SOA Suite domains with the operator is Oracle Linux 7 (UL6+) and Red Hat Enterprise Linux 7 (UL3+ only with standalone Kubernetes).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploy using Maven and Ant</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/deploying-composites/deploy-using-maven-ant/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/deploying-composites/deploy-using-maven-ant/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to deploy Oracle SOA Suite and Oracle Service Bus composite applications using the Maven and Ant based approach in an Oracle SOA Suite in WebLogic Kubernetes Operator environment.
Before deploying composite applications, we need to create a Kubernetes pod in the same cluster where the Oracle SOA Suite domain is running, so that composite applications can be deployed using the internal Kubernetes Service for the Administration Server URL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enable additional URL access</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/enable-additional-url-access/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/enable-additional-url-access/</guid>
      <description>This section provides information about how to extend an existing ingress (Non-SSL and SSL termination) to enable additional application URL access for Oracle SOA Suite domains.
The ingress per domain created in the steps in Set up a load balancer exposes the application paths defined in template YAML files present at ${WORKDIR}/charts/ingress-per-domain/templates/.
To extend an existing ingress with additional application URL access:
  Update the template YAML file at ${WORKDIR}/charts/ingress-per-domain/templates/ to define additional path rules.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NGINX</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/configure-load-balancer/nginx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/configure-load-balancer/nginx/</guid>
      <description>This section provides information about how to install and configure the ingress-based NGINX load balancer to load balance Oracle SOA Suite domain clusters. You can configure NGINX for non-SSL, SSL termination, and end-to-end SSL access of the application URL.
Follow these steps to set up NGINX as a load balancer for an Oracle SOA Suite domain in a Kubernetes cluster:
See the official installation document for prerequisites.
 Install the NGINX load balancer for non-SSL and SSL termination configuration Generate secret for SSL access Install NGINX load balancer for end-to-end SSL configuration Configure NGINX to manage ingresses Verify domain application URL access Uninstall NGINX ingress Uninstall NGINX  To get repository information, enter the following Helm commands:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade an operator release</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/patch_and_upgrade/upgrade-operator-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/patch_and_upgrade/upgrade-operator-release/</guid>
      <description>To upgrade the WebLogic Kubernetes operator, use the helm upgrade command with new Helm chart and operator image. See the steps here to pull the operator image and set up the Oracle SOA Suite repository that contains the operator chart. To upgrade the operator run the following command:
$ cd ${WORKDIR} $ helm upgrade \ --reuse-values \ --set image=oracle/weblogic-kubernetes-operator:3.3.0 \ --namespace weblogic-operator-namespace \ --wait \ weblogic-kubernetes-operator \ charts/weblogic-operator  Note: When the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator is upgraded from release version 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>b. Using Design Console with NGINX(SSL)</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oig/configure-design-console/using-the-design-console-with-nginx-ssl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oig/configure-design-console/using-the-design-console-with-nginx-ssl/</guid>
      <description>Configure an NGINX ingress (SSL) to allow Design Console to connect to your Kubernetes cluster.
  Prerequisites
  Setup routing rules for the Design Console ingress
  Create the ingress
  Update the T3 channel
  Restart the OIG domain
  Design Console client
a. Using an on-premises installed Design Console
b. Using a container image for Design Console
  Login to the Design Console</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WLST administration operations</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oig/manage-oig-domains/wlst-admin-operations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oig/manage-oig-domains/wlst-admin-operations/</guid>
      <description>Invoke WLST and access Administration Server To use WLST to administer the OIG domain, use a helper pod in the same Kubernetes cluster as the OIG Domain.
  Run the following command to create a helper pod if one doesn&amp;rsquo;t already exist:
$ kubectl run helper --image &amp;lt;image_name&amp;gt; -n &amp;lt;domain_namespace&amp;gt; -- sleep infinity For example:
$ kubectl run helper --image 12.2.1.4.0-8-ol7-211022.0723 -n oigns -- sleep infinity The output will look similar to the following:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploy using composites in a persistent volume or image</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/deploying-composites/deploy-artifacts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 12:04:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/deploying-composites/deploy-artifacts/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to deploy Oracle SOA Suite and Oracle Service Bus composite applications artifacts in a Kubernetes persistent volume or in an image to an Oracle SOA Suite environment deployed using a WebLogic Kubernetes Operator.
The deployment methods described in Deploy using JDeveloper and Deploy using Maven and Ant are manual processes. If you have the deployment artifacts (archives) already built, then you can package them either into a Kubernetes persistent volume or in an image and use this automated process to deploy the artifacts to an Oracle SOA Suite domain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache web tier</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/configure-load-balancer/apache/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/configure-load-balancer/apache/</guid>
      <description>This section provides information about how to install and configure the Apache web tier to load balance Oracle SOA Suite domain clusters. You can configure Apache web tier for non-SSL and SSL termination access of the application URL.
Follow these steps to set up the Apache web tier as a load balancer for an Oracle SOA Suite domain in a Kubernetes cluster:
 Build the Apache web tier image Create the Apache plugin configuration file Prepare the certificate and private key Install the Apache web tier Helm chart Verify domain application URL access Uninstall Apache web tier  Build the Apache web tier image Refer to the sample, to build the Apache web tier Docker image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configure SSL certificates</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/configuring-custom-ssl-certificates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/configuring-custom-ssl-certificates/</guid>
      <description>Secure Socket Layer (SSL) provides a secured communication for data sent over unsecured networks. In an SSL termination scenario, you can configure SSL between the client browser and the load balancer in your Oracle SOA Suite instance to ensure that applications are accessed securely. In an SSL end-to-end scenario, an Oracle SOA Suite domain is configured to use a self-signed SSL certificate that was generated during domain creation. Clients will typically receive a message indicating that the signing CA for the certificate is unknown and not trusted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security hardening</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/appendix/docker-k8s-hardening/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/appendix/docker-k8s-hardening/</guid>
      <description>Securing a Kubernetes cluster involves hardening on multiple fronts - securing the API servers, etcd, nodes, container images, container run-time, and the cluster network. Apply principles of defense in depth, principle of least privilege, and minimize the attack surface. Use security tools such as Kube-Bench to verify the cluster&amp;rsquo;s security posture. Since Kubernetes is evolving rapidly refer to Kubernetes Security Overview for the latest information on securing a Kubernetes cluster. Also ensure the deployed Docker containers follow the Docker Security guidance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade a Kubernetes cluster</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/patch_and_upgrade/upgrade-k8s-cluster/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/patch_and_upgrade/upgrade-k8s-cluster/</guid>
      <description>These instructions describe how to upgrade a Kubernetes cluster created using kubeadm on which an Oracle SOA Suite domain is deployed. A rolling upgrade approach is used to upgrade nodes (master and worker) of the Kubernetes cluster.
It is expected that there will be a down time during the upgrade of the Kubernetes cluster as the nodes need to be drained as part of the upgrade process.
 Prerequisites  Review Prerequisites and ensure that your Kubernetes cluster is ready for upgrade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Runnning OIG utilities</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oig/manage-oig-domains/running-oig-utilities/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oig/manage-oig-domains/running-oig-utilities/</guid>
      <description>Run OIG utlities inside the OIG Kubernetes cluster.
Run utilities in an interactive bash shell   Access a bash shell inside the governancedomain-oim-server1 pod:
$ kubectl -n oigns exec -it governancedomain-oim-server1 -- bash This will take you into a bash shell in the running governancedomain-oim-server1 pod:
[oracle@governancedomain-oim-server1 oracle]$   Navigate to the /u01/oracle/idm/server/bin directory and execute the utility as required. For example:
[oracle@governancedomain-oim-server1 oracle] cd /u01/oracle/idm/server/bin [oracle@governancedomain-oim-server1 bin]$ .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitor a domain and publish logs</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/monitoring-soa-domains/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/monitoring-soa-domains/</guid>
      <description>After the Oracle SOA Suite domain is set up, you can:
 Monitor the Oracle SOA Suite instance using Prometheus and Grafana Publish WebLogic Server logs into Elasticsearch Publish SOA server diagnostics logs into Elasticsearch  Monitor the Oracle SOA Suite instance using Prometheus and Grafana Using the WebLogic Monitoring Exporter you can scrape runtime information from a running Oracle SOA Suite instance and monitor them using Prometheus and Grafana.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logging and visualization</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oig/manage-oig-domains/logging-and-visualization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oig/manage-oig-domains/logging-and-visualization/</guid>
      <description>After the OIG domain is set up you can publish operator and WebLogic Server logs into Elasticsearch and interact with them in Kibana.
In Prepare your environment if you decided to use the Elasticsearch and Kibana by setting the parameter elkIntegrationEnabled to true, then the steps below must be followed to complete the setup.
If you did not set elkIntegrationEnabled to true and want to do so post configuration, run the following command from the $WORKDIR directory:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expose the T3/T3S protocol</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/enablingt3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/enablingt3/</guid>
      <description>Oracle strongly recommends that you do not expose non-HTTPS traffic (T3/T3s/LDAP/IIOP/IIOPs) outside of the external firewall. You can control this access using a combination of network channels and firewalls.
 You can create T3/T3S channels and the corresponding Kubernetes service to expose the T3/T3S protocol for the Administration Server and Managed Servers in an Oracle SOA Suite domain.
The WebLogic Kubernetes Operator provides an option to expose a T3 channel for the Administration Server using the exposeAdminT3Channel setting during domain creation, then the matching T3 service can be used to connect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitoring an OIG domain</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oig/manage-oig-domains/monitoring-oim-domains/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oig/manage-oig-domains/monitoring-oim-domains/</guid>
      <description>After the OIG domain is set up you can monitor the OIG instance using Prometheus and Grafana. See Monitoring a domain.
The WebLogic Monitoring Exporter uses the WLS RESTful Management API to scrape runtime information and then exports Prometheus-compatible metrics. It is deployed as a web application in a WebLogic Server (WLS) instance, version 12.2.1 or later, typically, in the instance from which you want to get metrics.
There are two ways to setup monitoring and you should choose one method or the other:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uninstall</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/cleanup-domain-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/cleanup-domain-setup/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to clean up the Oracle SOA Suite domain setup.
Remove the domain   Remove the domain&amp;rsquo;s ingress (for example, Traefik ingress) using Helm:
$ helm uninstall soa-domain-ingress -n sample-domain1-ns For example:
$ helm uninstall soainfra-traefik -n soans   Remove the domain resources by using the sample delete-weblogic-domain-resources.sh script present at ${WORKDIR}/delete-domain:
$ cd ${WORKDIR}/delete-domain $ ./delete-weblogic-domain-resources.sh -d sample-domain1 For example:
$ cd ${WORKDIR}/delete-domain $ ./delete-weblogic-domain-resources.sh -d soainfra   Use kubectl to confirm that the server pods and domain resource are deleted:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delete the OIG domain home</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oig/manage-oig-domains/delete-domain-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oig/manage-oig-domains/delete-domain-home/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes in production, but most likely in testing environments, you might want to remove the domain home that is generated using the create-domain.sh script.
  Run the following command to delete the domain:
$ cd $WORKDIR/kubernetes/delete-domain $ ./delete-weblogic-domain-resources.sh -d &amp;lt;domain_uid&amp;gt; For example:
$ cd $WORKDIR/kubernetes/delete-domain $ ./delete-weblogic-domain-resources.sh -d governancedomain   Drop the RCU schemas as follows:
$ kubectl exec -it helper -n &amp;lt;domain_namespace&amp;gt; -- /bin/bash [oracle@helper ~]$ [oracle@helper ~]$ export CONNECTION_STRING=&amp;lt;db_host.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frequently Asked Questions</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/faq/</guid>
      <description>Overriding tuning parameters is not supported using configuration overrides The WebLogic Kubernetes Operator enables you to override some of the domain configuration using configuration overrides (also called situational configuration). See supported overrides. Overriding the tuning parameters such as MaxMessageSize and PAYLOAD, for Oracle SOA Suite domains is not supported using the configuration overrides feature. However, you can override them using the following steps:
  Specify the new value using the environment variable K8S_REFCONF_OVERRIDES in serverPod.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Persist adapter customizations</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/persisting-soa-adapters-customizations/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/persisting-soa-adapters-customizations/</guid>
      <description>The lifetime for any customization done in a file on a server pod is up to the lifetime of that pod. The changes are not persisted once the pod goes down or is restarted.
For example, the following configuration updates DbAdapter.rar to create a new connection instance and creates data source CoffeeShop on the Administration Console for the same with jdbc/CoffeeShopDS.
File location: /u01/oracle/soa/soa/connectors/DbAdapter.rar
&amp;lt;connection-instance&amp;gt; &amp;lt;jndi-name&amp;gt;eis/DB/CoffeeShop&amp;lt;/jndi-name&amp;gt; &amp;lt;connection-properties&amp;gt; &amp;lt;properties&amp;gt; &amp;lt;property&amp;gt; &amp;lt;name&amp;gt;XADataSourceName&amp;lt;/name&amp;gt; &amp;lt;value&amp;gt;jdbc/CoffeeShopDS&amp;lt;/value&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/property&amp;gt; &amp;lt;property&amp;gt; &amp;lt;name&amp;gt;DataSourceName&amp;lt;/name&amp;gt; &amp;lt;value&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/value&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/property&amp;gt; &amp;lt;property&amp;gt; &amp;lt;name&amp;gt;PlatformClassName&amp;lt;/name&amp;gt; &amp;lt;value&amp;gt;org.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perform WLST operations</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/performing-wlst-operations/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/performing-wlst-operations/</guid>
      <description>You can use the WebLogic Scripting Tool (WLST) to manage a domain running in a Kubernetes cluster. Some of the many ways to do this are provided here.
If the Administration Server was configured to expose a T3 channel using exposeAdminT3Channel when creating the domain, refer to Use WLST.
If you do not want to expose additional ports and perform WLST administration operations using the existing Kubernetes services created by the WebLogic Server Kubernetes operator, then follow this documentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>a) Logging and Visualization for Helm Chart oud-ds-rs Deployment</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oud/manage-oud-containers/logging-and-visualization/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oud/manage-oud-containers/logging-and-visualization/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Installation  Enable Elasticsearch, Logstash, and Kibana Create Data Mount Points Configure Logstash Install or Upgrade Oracle Unified Directory Container with ELK Configuration Configure ElasticSearch   Verify Using the Kibana Application  Introduction This section describes how to install and configure logging and visualization for the oud-ds-rs Helm Chart deployment.
The ELK stack consists of Elasticsearch, Logstash, and Kibana. Using ELK we can gain insights in real-time from the log data from your applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>a) Logging and Visualization for Helm Chart oudsm Deployment</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oudsm/manage-oudsm-containers/logging-and-visualization/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oudsm/manage-oudsm-containers/logging-and-visualization/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Installation  Enable Elasticsearch, Logstash, and Kibana Create Data Mount Points Configure Logstash Install or Upgrade Oracle Unified Directory Services Manager Container with ELK Configuration Configure ElasticSearch   Verify Using the Kibana Application  Introduction This section describes how to install and configure logging and visualization for the oudsm Helm Chart deployment.
The ELK stack consists of Elasticsearch, Logstash, and Kibana. Using ELK we can gain insights in real-time from the log data from your applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>b) Monitoring an Oracle Unified Directory Instance</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oud/manage-oud-containers/monitoring-oud-instance/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oud/manage-oud-containers/monitoring-oud-instance/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Install Prometheus and Grafana  Create a Kubernetes Namespace Add Prometheus and Grafana Helm Repositories Install the Prometheus Operator View Prometheus and Grafana Objects Created Add the NodePort   Verify Using Grafana GUI  Introduction After the Oracle Unified Directory instance is set up you can monitor it using Prometheus and Grafana.
Install Prometheus and Grafana Create a Kubernetes Namespace Create a Kubernetes namespace to provide a scope for Prometheus and Grafana objects such as pods and services that you create in the environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>b) Monitoring an Oracle Unified Directory Services Manager Instance</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oudsm/manage-oudsm-containers/monitoring-oudsm-instance/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oudsm/manage-oudsm-containers/monitoring-oudsm-instance/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Install Prometheus and Grafana  Create a Kubernetes Namespace Add Prometheus and Grafana Helm Repositories Install the Prometheus Operator View Prometheus and Grafana Objects Created Add the NodePort   Verify Using Grafana GUI  Introduction After the Oracle Unified Directory Services Manager instance is set up you can monitor it using Prometheus and Grafana.
Install Prometheus and Grafana Create a Kubernetes Namespace Create a Kubernetes namespace to provide a scope for Prometheus and Grafana objects such as pods and services that you create in the environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>a. Domain Life Cycle</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oam/manage-oam-domains/domain-lifecycle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oam/manage-oam-domains/domain-lifecycle/</guid>
      <description>As OAM domains use the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator, domain lifecyle operations are managed using the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator itself.
This document shows the basic operations for starting, stopping and scaling servers in the OAM domain.
For more detailed information refer to Domain Life Cycle in the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator documentation.
Do not use the WebLogic Server Administration Console or Oracle Enterprise Manager Console to start or stop servers.
 View existing OAM servers The default OAM deployment starts the Administration Server (AdminServer), two OAM Managed Servers (oam_server1 and oam_server2) and two OAM Policy Manager server (oam_policy_mgr1 and oam_policy_mgr2 ).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>a. Patch an image</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oam/patch-and-upgrade/patch_an_image/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oam/patch-and-upgrade/patch_an_image/</guid>
      <description>To update your OAM Kubernetes cluster with a new OAM Docker image, first install the new Docker image on all nodes in your Kubernetes cluster.
Once the new image is installed, choose one of the following options to update your OAM kubernetes cluster to use the new image:
 Run the kubectl edit domain command Run the kubectl patch domain command  In all of the above cases, the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator will restart the Administration Server pod first and then perform a rolling restart on the OAM Managed Servers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>a. Patch an image</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oig/patch-and-upgrade/patch_an_image/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oig/patch-and-upgrade/patch_an_image/</guid>
      <description>To update your OIG Kubernetes cluster with a new OIG Docker image, first install the new Docker image on all nodes in your Kubernetes cluster.
Once the new image is installed choose one of the following options to update your OIG Kubernetes cluster to use the new image:
 Run the kubectl edit domain command Run the kubectl patch domain command  In all of the above cases, the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator will restart the Administration Server pod first and then perform a rolling restart on the OIG Managed Servers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>a. Post Install Tasks</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oig/post-install-config/set_oimfronendurl_using_mbeans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oig/post-install-config/set_oimfronendurl_using_mbeans/</guid>
      <description>Follow these post install configuration steps.
 Create a Server Overrides File Set OIMFrontendURL using MBeans  Create a Server Overrides File   Navigate to the following directory:
cd $WORKDIR/kubernetes/create-oim-domain/domain-home-on-pv/output/weblogic-domains/governancedomain   Create a setUserOverrides.sh with the following contents:
DERBY_FLAG=false JAVA_OPTIONS=&amp;quot;${JAVA_OPTIONS} -Djava.net.preferIPv4Stack=true&amp;quot; MEM_ARGS=&amp;quot;-Xms8192m -Xmx8192m&amp;quot;   Copy the setUserOverrides.sh file to the Administration Server pod:
$ chmod 755 setUserOverrides.sh $ kubectl cp setUserOverrides.sh oigns/governancedomain-adminserver:/u01/oracle/user_projects/domains/governancedomain/bin/setUserOverrides.sh Where oigns is the OIG namespace and governancedomain is the domain_UID.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>a. Using an Ingress with NGINX (non-SSL)</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oig/configure-ingress/ingress-nginx-setup-for-oig-domain-setup-on-k8s/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oig/configure-ingress/ingress-nginx-setup-for-oig-domain-setup-on-k8s/</guid>
      <description>Setting up an ingress for NGINX for the OIG domain on Kubernetes (non-SSL) The instructions below explain how to set up NGINX as an ingress for the OIG domain with non-SSL termination.
Note: All the steps below should be performed on the master node.
  Install NGINX
a. Configure the repository
b. Create a namespace
c. Install NGINX using helm
d. Setup routing rules for the domain
  Create an ingress for the domain</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>b. Install and configure connectors</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oig/post-install-config/install_and_configure_connectors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oig/post-install-config/install_and_configure_connectors/</guid>
      <description>Download the connector   Download the Connector you are interested in from Oracle Identity Manager Connector Downloads.
  Copy the connector zip file to a staging directory on the master node e.g. &amp;lt;workdir&amp;gt;/stage and unzip it:
$ cp $HOME/Downloads/&amp;lt;connector&amp;gt;.zip &amp;lt;workdir&amp;gt;/&amp;lt;stage&amp;gt;/ $ cd &amp;lt;workdir&amp;gt;/&amp;lt;stage&amp;gt; $ unzip &amp;lt;connector&amp;gt;.zip For example:
$ cp $HOME/Downloads/Exchange-12.2.1.3.0.zip /scratch/OIGK8S/stage/ $ cd /scratch/OIGK8S/stage/ $ unzip exchange-12.2.1.3.0.zip   Create a directory in the persistent volume   On the master node run the following command to create a ConnectorDefaultDirectory:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>b. Upgrade an operator release</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oam/patch-and-upgrade/upgrade_an_operator_release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oam/patch-and-upgrade/upgrade_an_operator_release/</guid>
      <description>These instructions apply to upgrading the operator within the 3.x release family as additional versions are released.
The new WebLogic Kubernetes Operator Docker image must be installed on the master node and each of the worker nodes in your Kubernetes cluster. Alternatively you can place the image in a Docker registry that your cluster can access.
   Pull the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator 3.X.X image by running the following command on the master node:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>b. Upgrade an operator release</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oig/patch-and-upgrade/upgrade_an_operator_release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oig/patch-and-upgrade/upgrade_an_operator_release/</guid>
      <description>These instructions apply to upgrading operators within the 3.x release family as additional versions are released.
The new WebLogic Kubernetes Operator Docker image must be installed on the master node AND each of the worker nodes in your Kubernetes cluster. Alternatively you can place the image in a Docker registry that your cluster can access.
   Pull the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator 3.X.X image by running the following command on the master node:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>b. Using an Ingress with NGINX (SSL)</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oig/configure-ingress/ingress-nginx-setup-for-oig-domain-setup-on-k8s-ssl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oig/configure-ingress/ingress-nginx-setup-for-oig-domain-setup-on-k8s-ssl/</guid>
      <description>Setting up an ingress for NGINX for the OIG domain on Kubernetes The instructions below explain how to set up NGINX as an ingress for the OIG domain with SSL termination.
Note: All the steps below should be performed on the master node.
  Create a SSL certificate
a. Generate SSL certificate
b. Create a Kubernetes secret for SSL
  Install NGINX
a. Configure the repository
b. Create a namespace</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>b. WLST Administration Operations</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oam/manage-oam-domains/wlst-admin-operations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oam/manage-oam-domains/wlst-admin-operations/</guid>
      <description>To use WLST to administer the OAM domain, use the helper pod in the same Kubernetes cluster as the OAM Domain.
  Run the following command to start a bash shell in the helper pod:
$ kubectl exec -it helper -n &amp;lt;domain_namespace&amp;gt; -- /bin/bash For example:
$ kubectl exec -it helper -n oamns -- /bin/bash This will take you into a bash shell in the running helper pod:
[oracle@helper ~]$   Connect to WLST using the following command:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>c. Logging and Visualization</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oam/manage-oam-domains/logging-and-visualization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oam/manage-oam-domains/logging-and-visualization/</guid>
      <description>After the OAM domain is set up you can publish operator and WebLogic Server logs into Elasticsearch and interact with them in Kibana.
In Prepare your environment if you decided to use the Elasticsearch and Kibana by setting the parameter elkIntegrationEnabled to true, then the steps below must be followed to complete the setup.
If you did not set elkIntegrationEnabled to true and want to do so post configuration, run the following command from the $WORKDIR directory:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>d. Monitoring an OAM domain</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oam/manage-oam-domains/monitoring-oam-domains/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oam/manage-oam-domains/monitoring-oam-domains/</guid>
      <description>After the OAM domain is set up you can monitor the OAM instance using Prometheus and Grafana. See Monitoring a domain.
The WebLogic Monitoring Exporter uses the WLS RESTful Management API to scrape runtime information and then exports Prometheus-compatible metrics. It is deployed as a web application in a WebLogic Server (WLS) instance, version 12.2.1 or later, typically, in the instance from which you want to get metrics.
There are two ways to setup monitoring and you should choose one method or the other:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>e. Delete the OAM domain home</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oam/manage-oam-domains/delete-domain-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oam/manage-oam-domains/delete-domain-home/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes in production, but most likely in testing environments, you might want to remove the domain home that is generated using the create-domain.sh script.
  Run the following command to delete the domain:
$ cd $WORKDIR/kubernetes/delete-domain $ ./delete-weblogic-domain-resources.sh -d &amp;lt;domain_uid&amp;gt; For example:
$ cd $WORKDIR/kubernetes/delete-domain $ ./delete-weblogic-domain-resources.sh -d accessdomain   Drop the RCU schemas as follows:
$ kubectl exec -it helper -n &amp;lt;domain_namespace&amp;gt; -- /bin/bash [oracle@helper ~]$ [oracle@helper ~]$ export CONNECTION_STRING=&amp;lt;db_host.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>