<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Set up a load balancer on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.2/wcsites-domains/adminguide/configure-load-balancer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Set up a load balancer on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.2/wcsites-domains/adminguide/configure-load-balancer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Traefik</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.2/wcsites-domains/adminguide/configure-load-balancer/traefik/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.2/wcsites-domains/adminguide/configure-load-balancer/traefik/</guid>
      <description>This section provides information about how to install and configure the ingress-based Traefik load balancer (version 2.2.1 or later for production deployments) to load balance Oracle WebCenter Sites domain clusters. You can configure Traefik for access of the application URL.
Follow these steps to set up Traefik as a load balancer for an Oracle WebCenter Sites domain in a Kubernetes cluster:
Setting Up Loadbalancer Traefik for the WebCenter Sites Domain on K8S Follow these steps to set up Traefik as a loadbalancer for the Oracle WebCenter Sites domain:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NGINX</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.2/wcsites-domains/adminguide/configure-load-balancer/nginx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.2/wcsites-domains/adminguide/configure-load-balancer/nginx/</guid>
      <description>This section provides information about how to install and configure the ingress-based NGINX load balancer to load balance Oracle WebCenter Sites domain clusters. You can configure NGINX for access of the application URL.
Follow these steps to set up NGINX as a load balancer for an Oracle WebCenter Sites domain in a Kubernetes cluster:
See the official installation document for prerequisites.
Add the Helm repos (if not added) Add following Helm repos</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>