<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Configure an Ingress for an OIG domain on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.1/oig/configure-ingress/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Configure an Ingress for an OIG domain on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.1/oig/configure-ingress/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>a. Using an Ingress with NGINX (non-SSL)</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.1/oig/configure-ingress/ingress-nginx-setup-for-oig-domain-setup-on-k8s/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.1/oig/configure-ingress/ingress-nginx-setup-for-oig-domain-setup-on-k8s/</guid>
      <description>Setting Up an ingress for NGINX for the OIG Domain on Kubernetes (non-SSL) The instructions below explain how to set up NGINX as an ingress for the OIG domain with non-SSL termination.
Note: All the steps below should be performed on the master node.
 Install NGINX  Configure the repository Create a Namespace Install NGINX using helm Setup Routing Rules for the Domain   Create an Ingress for the Domain Verify that You can Access the Domain URL Cleanup  Install NGINX Use helm to install NGINX.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>b. Using an Ingress with NGINX (SSL)</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.1/oig/configure-ingress/ingress-nginx-setup-for-oig-domain-setup-on-k8s-ssl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.1/oig/configure-ingress/ingress-nginx-setup-for-oig-domain-setup-on-k8s-ssl/</guid>
      <description>Setting Up an Ingress for NGINX for the OIG Domain on Kubernetes The instructions below explain how to set up NGINX as an ingress for the OIG domain with SSL termination.
Note: All the steps below should be performed on the master node.
 Create a SSL Certificate  Generate SSL Certificate Create a Kubernetes Secret for SSL   Install NGINX  Configure the repository Create a Namespace Install NGINX using helm   Create an Ingress for the Domain Verify that You can Access the Domain URL Cleanup  Create a SSL Certificate Generate SSL Certificate   Generate a private key and certificate signing request (CSR) using a tool of your choice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>c. Using an Ingress with Voyager (non-SSL)</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.1/oig/configure-ingress/ingress-voyager-setup-for-oig-domain-setup-on-k8s/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.1/oig/configure-ingress/ingress-voyager-setup-for-oig-domain-setup-on-k8s/</guid>
      <description>Setting Up an Ingress for Voyager for the OIG Domain on Kubernetes The instructions below explain how to set up Voyager as an Ingress for the OIG domain with non-SSL termination.
Note: All the steps below should be performed on the master node.
 Install Voyager  Configure the repository Create Namespace and Install Voyager Setup Routing Rules for the Domain   Create an Ingress for the Domain Verify that You can Access the Domain URL Cleanup  Install Voyager Use Helm to install Voyager.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>d. Using an Ingress with Voyager (SSL)</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.1/oig/configure-ingress/ingress-voyager-setup-for-oig-domain-setup-on-k8s-ssl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.1/oig/configure-ingress/ingress-voyager-setup-for-oig-domain-setup-on-k8s-ssl/</guid>
      <description>Setting Up an Ingress for Voyager for the OIG Domain on Kubernetes The instructions below explain how to set up Voyager as an Ingress for the OIG domain with SSL termination.
Note: All the steps below should be performed on the master node.
 Create a SSL Certificate  Generate SSL Certificate Create a Kubernetes Secret for SSL   Install Voyager  Configure the repository Create Namespace and Install Voyager Setup Routing Rules for the Domain   Create an Ingress for the Domain Verify that You can Access the Domain URL Cleanup  Create a SSL Certificate Generate SSL Certificate   Generate a private key and certificate signing request (CSR) using a tool of your choice.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>