<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Oracle Cloud Infrastructure on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.3/wccontent-domains/oracle-cloud/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Oracle Cloud Infrastructure on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 16:43:45 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.3/wccontent-domains/oracle-cloud/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparing an OKE environment</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.3/wccontent-domains/oracle-cloud/prepare-oke-environment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 16:43:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.3/wccontent-domains/oracle-cloud/prepare-oke-environment/</guid>
      <description>Contents  Create Public SSH Key to access all the Bastion and Worker nodes Create a compartment for OKE Create Container Clusters (OKE) Create Bastion Node to access Cluster Setup OCI CLI to download kubeconfig and access OKE Cluster  Create Public SSH Key to access all the Bastion and Worker nodes Create SSH key using ssh-keygen on linux terminal to access (ssh) the Compute instances (worker/bastion) in OCI.
ssh-keygen -t rsa -N &amp;#34;&amp;#34; -b 2048 -C demokey -f id_rsa Create a compartment for OKE Within your tenancy, there must be a compartment to contain the necessary network resources (VCN, subnets, internet gateway, route table, security lists).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparing a file system</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.3/wccontent-domains/oracle-cloud/filesystem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.3/wccontent-domains/oracle-cloud/filesystem/</guid>
      <description>Create Filesystem and security list for FSS  Note: Make sure you create the filesystem and security list in the OKE created VCN
   Login to OCI Console and go to Storage and Click File System   Click Create File System   You can create File System and Mount Targets with the default values. But in case you want to rename the file System and mount targets, follow below steps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparing OCIR</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.3/wccontent-domains/oracle-cloud/ocir/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.3/wccontent-domains/oracle-cloud/ocir/</guid>
      <description>Publish images to OCIR Push all the required images to OCIR and subsequently use from there. Follow the below steps for pushing the images to OCIR
Create an &amp;ldquo;Auth token&amp;rdquo; Create an &amp;ldquo;Auth token&amp;rdquo; which will be used as docker password to push and pull images from OCIR. Login to OCI Console and navigate to User Settings, which is in the drop down under your OCI user-profile, located at the top-right corner of the OCI console page.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>