<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Patch and Upgrade on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oam/patch-and-upgrade/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Patch and Upgrade on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oam/patch-and-upgrade/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>a. Patch an image</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oam/patch-and-upgrade/patch_an_image/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oam/patch-and-upgrade/patch_an_image/</guid>
      <description>To update your OAM Kubernetes cluster with a new OAM Docker image, first install the new Docker image on all nodes in your Kubernetes cluster.
Once the new image is installed, choose one of the following options to update your OAM kubernetes cluster to use the new image:
 Run the kubectl edit domain command Run the kubectl patch domain command  In all of the above cases, the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator will restart the Administration Server pod first and then perform a rolling restart on the OAM Managed Servers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>b. Upgrade an operator release</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oam/patch-and-upgrade/upgrade_an_operator_release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/oam/patch-and-upgrade/upgrade_an_operator_release/</guid>
      <description>These instructions apply to upgrading the operator within the 3.x release family as additional versions are released.
The new WebLogic Kubernetes Operator Docker image must be installed on the master node and each of the worker nodes in your Kubernetes cluster. Alternatively you can place the image in a Docker registry that your cluster can access.
   Pull the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator 3.X.X image by running the following command on the master node:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>