<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Manage Oracle Unified Directory Services Manager Containers on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>/fmw-kubernetes/20.4.1/oudsm/manage-oudsm-containers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Manage Oracle Unified Directory Services Manager Containers on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 06:46:23 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/fmw-kubernetes/20.4.1/oudsm/manage-oudsm-containers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>a) Logging and Visualization for Helm Chart oudsm Deployment</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/20.4.1/oudsm/manage-oudsm-containers/logging-and-visualization/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/20.4.1/oudsm/manage-oudsm-containers/logging-and-visualization/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Installation  Enable Elasticsearch, Logstash, and Kibana Create Data Mount Points Configure Logstash Install or Upgrade Oracle Unified Directory Services Manager Container with ELK Configuration Configure ElasticSearch   Verify Using the Kibana Application  Introduction This section describes how to install and configure logging and visualization for the oudsm Helm Chart deployment.
The ELK stack consists of Elasticsearch, Logstash, and Kibana. Using ELK we can gain insights in real-time from the log data from your applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>b) Monitoring an Oracle Unified Directory Services Manager Instance</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/20.4.1/oudsm/manage-oudsm-containers/monitoring-oudsm-instance/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/20.4.1/oudsm/manage-oudsm-containers/monitoring-oudsm-instance/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Install Prometheus and Grafana  Create a Kubernetes Namespace Add Prometheus and Grafana Helm Repositories Install the Prometheus Operator View Prometheus and Grafana Objects Created Add the NodePort   Verify Using Grafana GUI  Introduction After the Oracle Unified Directory Services Manager instance is set up you can monitor it using Prometheus and Grafana.
Install Prometheus and Grafana Create a Kubernetes Namespace Create a Kubernetes namespace to provide a scope for Prometheus and Grafana objects such as pods and services that you create in the environment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>