<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Set up a load balancer on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/configure-load-balancer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Set up a load balancer on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/configure-load-balancer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Traefik</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/configure-load-balancer/traefik/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/configure-load-balancer/traefik/</guid>
      <description>This section provides information about how to install and configure the ingress-based Traefik load balancer (version 2.2.1 or later for production deployments) to load balance Oracle SOA Suite domain clusters. You can configure Traefik for non-SSL, SSL termination, and end-to-end SSL access of the application URL.
Follow these steps to set up Traefik as a load balancer for an Oracle SOA Suite domain in a Kubernetes cluster:
 Install the Traefik (ingress-based) load balancer Create an Ingress for the domain Verify domain application URL access Uninstall the Traefik ingress Uninstall Traefik  Install the Traefik (ingress-based) load balancer   Use Helm to install the Traefik (ingress-based) load balancer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NGINX</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/configure-load-balancer/nginx/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/configure-load-balancer/nginx/</guid>
      <description>This section provides information about how to install and configure the ingress-based NGINX load balancer to load balance Oracle SOA Suite domain clusters. You can configure NGINX for non-SSL, SSL termination, and end-to-end SSL access of the application URL.
Follow these steps to set up NGINX as a load balancer for an Oracle SOA Suite domain in a Kubernetes cluster:
See the official installation document for prerequisites.
 Install the NGINX load balancer for non-SSL and SSL termination configuration Generate secret for SSL access Install NGINX load balancer for end-to-end SSL configuration Configure NGINX to manage ingresses Verify domain application URL access Uninstall NGINX ingress Uninstall NGINX  To get repository information, enter the following Helm commands:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache web tier</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/configure-load-balancer/apache/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 15:44:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.4.2/soa-domains/adminguide/configure-load-balancer/apache/</guid>
      <description>This section provides information about how to install and configure the Apache web tier to load balance Oracle SOA Suite domain clusters. You can configure Apache web tier for non-SSL and SSL termination access of the application URL.
Follow these steps to set up the Apache web tier as a load balancer for an Oracle SOA Suite domain in a Kubernetes cluster:
 Build the Apache web tier image Create the Apache plugin configuration file Prepare the certificate and private key Install the Apache web tier Helm chart Verify domain application URL access Uninstall Apache web tier  Build the Apache web tier image Refer to the sample, to build the Apache web tier Docker image.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>