<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Manage Oracle Unified Directory Services Manager Containers on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.1/oudsm/manage-oudsm-containers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Manage Oracle Unified Directory Services Manager Containers on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.1/oudsm/manage-oudsm-containers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>a) Scaling Up/Down OUDSM Pods </title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.1/oudsm/manage-oudsm-containers/scaling-up-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.1/oudsm/manage-oudsm-containers/scaling-up-down/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This section describes how to increase or decrease the number of OUDSM pods in the Kubernetes deployment.
View existing OUDSM pods By default the oudsm helm chart deployment starts one pod: oudsm-1.
The number of pods started is determined by the replicaCount, which is set to 1 by default. A value of 1 starts the pod above.
To scale up or down the number of OUDSM pods, set replicaCount accordingly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>b) Logging and Visualization for Helm Chart oudsm Deployment</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.1/oudsm/manage-oudsm-containers/logging-and-visualization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.1/oudsm/manage-oudsm-containers/logging-and-visualization/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Installation  Create a Kubernetes secret Enable Elasticsearch, Logstash, and Kibana Upgrade OUDSM deployment with ELK configuration Verify the pods   Verify using the Kibana application  Introduction This section describes how to install and configure logging and visualization for the oudsm Helm Chart deployment.
The ELK stack consists of Elasticsearch, Logstash, and Kibana. Using ELK we can gain insights in real-time from the log data from your applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>c) Monitoring an Oracle Unified Directory Services Manager Instance</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.1/oudsm/manage-oudsm-containers/monitoring-oudsm-instance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/22.2.1/oudsm/manage-oudsm-containers/monitoring-oudsm-instance/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Install Prometheus and Grafana  Create a Kubernetes namespace Add Prometheus and Grafana Helm repositories Install the Prometheus operator View Prometheus and Grafana Objects Created Add the NodePort   Verify Using Grafana GUI  Introduction After the Oracle Unified Directory Services Manager instance is set up you can monitor it using Prometheus and Grafana.
Install Prometheus and Grafana Create a Kubernetes namespace   Create a Kubernetes namespace to provide a scope for Prometheus and Grafana objects such as pods and services that you create in the environment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>