<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Manage OIG Domains on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>/fmw-kubernetes/20.4.1/oig/manage-oig-domains/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Manage OIG Domains on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/fmw-kubernetes/20.4.1/oig/manage-oig-domains/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Domain Life Cycle</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/20.4.1/oig/manage-oig-domains/domain-lifecycle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/20.4.1/oig/manage-oig-domains/domain-lifecycle/</guid>
      <description>View Existing OIG Servers Starting/Scaling up OIG Managed Servers Stopping/Scaling down OIG Managed Servers Stopping and Starting the AdminServer and Managed Servers  As OIG domains use the Oracle WebLogic Kubernetes Operator, domain lifecyle operations are managed using the Oracle WebLogic Kubernetes Operator itself.
This document shows the basic operations for starting, stopping and scaling servers in the OIG domain.
For more detailed information refer to Domain Life Cycle in the Oracle WebLogic Kubernetes Operator documentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WLST Administration Operations</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/20.4.1/oig/manage-oig-domains/wlst-admin-operations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/20.4.1/oig/manage-oig-domains/wlst-admin-operations/</guid>
      <description>Invoke WLST and Access Administration Server To use WLST to administer the OIG domain, use a helper pod in the same Kubernetes cluster as the OIG Domain.
  Run the following command to create a helper pod if one doesn&amp;rsquo;t already exist:
$ kubectl run helper --image &amp;lt;image_name&amp;gt; -n &amp;lt;domain_namespace&amp;gt; -- sleep infinity For example:
$ kubectl run helper --image oracle/oig:12.2.1.4.0 -n oimcluster -- sleep infinity The output will look similar to the following:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Runnning OIG Utilities</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/20.4.1/oig/manage-oig-domains/running-oig-utilities/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/20.4.1/oig/manage-oig-domains/running-oig-utilities/</guid>
      <description>Run OIG utlities inside the OIG Kubernetes cluster.
Run utilities in an interactive bash shell   Access a bash shell inside the oimcluster-oim-server1 pod:
$ kubectl -n oimcluster exec -it oimcluster-oim-server1 -- bash This will take you into a bash shell in the running oimcluster-oim-server1 pod:
[oracle@oimcluster-oim-server1 oracle]$   Navigate to the /u01/oracle/idm/server/bin directory and execute the utility as required. For example:
[oracle@oimcluster-oim-server1 oracle] cd /u01/oracle/idm/server/bin [oracle@oimcluster-oim-server1 bin]$ .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logging and Visualization</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/20.4.1/oig/manage-oig-domains/logging-and-visualization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/20.4.1/oig/manage-oig-domains/logging-and-visualization/</guid>
      <description>After the OIG domain is set up you can publish operator and WebLogic Server logs into Elasticsearch and interact with them in Kibana.
In Prepare your environment if you decided to use the Elasticsearch and Kibana by setting the parameter elkIntegrationEnabled to true, then the steps below must be followed to complete the setup.
If you did not set elkIntegrationEnabled to true and want to do so post configuration, run the following command:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitoring an OIG domain</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/20.4.1/oig/manage-oig-domains/monitoring-oim-domains/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/20.4.1/oig/manage-oig-domains/monitoring-oim-domains/</guid>
      <description>After the OIG domain is set up you can monitor the OIG instance using Prometheus and Grafana. See Monitoring a domain.
The WebLogic Monitoring Exporter uses the WLS RESTful Management API to scrape runtime information and then exports Prometheus-compatible metrics. It is deployed as a web application in a WebLogic Server (WLS) instance, version 12.2.1 or later, typically, in the instance from which you want to get metrics.
Deploy the Prometheus operator   Clone Prometheus by running the following commands:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delete the OIG domain home</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/20.4.1/oig/manage-oig-domains/delete-domain-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/20.4.1/oig/manage-oig-domains/delete-domain-home/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes in production, but most likely in testing environments, you might want to remove the domain home that is generated using the create-domain.sh script.
  Run the following command to delete the jobs, domain, and configmaps:
$ kubectl delete jobs &amp;lt;domain_job&amp;gt; -n &amp;lt;domain_namespace&amp;gt; $ kubectl delete domain &amp;lt;domain_uid&amp;gt; -n &amp;lt;domain_namespace&amp;gt; $ kubectl delete configmaps &amp;lt;domain_job&amp;gt;-cm -n &amp;lt;domain_namespace&amp;gt; For example:
$ kubectl delete jobs oimcluster-create-fmw-infra-sample-domain-job -n oimcluster $ kubectl delete domain oimcluster -n oimcluster $ kubectl delete configmaps oimcluster-create-fmw-infra-sample-domain-job-cm -n oimcluster   Drop the RCU schemas as follows:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>