<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Administration Guide on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</title>
    <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.2.3/wccontent-domains/adminguide/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Administration Guide on Oracle Fusion Middleware on Kubernetes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 16:43:45 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/fmw-kubernetes/21.2.3/wccontent-domains/adminguide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitor an Oracle WebCenter Content domain</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.2.3/wccontent-domains/adminguide/weblogic-monitoring-exporter-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.2.3/wccontent-domains/adminguide/weblogic-monitoring-exporter-setup/</guid>
      <description>You can monitor a WebCenter Content domain using Prometheus and Grafana by exporting the metrics from the domain instance using the WebLogic Monitoring Exporter. This sample shows you how to set up the WebLogic Monitoring Exporter to push the data to Prometheus.
Prerequisites This document assumes that the Prometheus Operator is deployed on the Kubernetes cluster. If it is not already deployed, follow the steps below for deploying the Prometheus Operator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elasticsearch integration for logs</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.2.3/wccontent-domains/adminguide/elasticsearch-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 16:43:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.2.3/wccontent-domains/adminguide/elasticsearch-integration/</guid>
      <description>1. Integrate Elasticsearch to WebLogic Kubernetes Operator For reference information, see Elasticsearch integration for the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator.
To enable elasticsearch integration, you must edit file kubernetes/charts/weblogic-operator/values.yaml before deploying the WebLogic Kubernetes Operator.
# elkIntegrationEnabled specifies whether or not ELK integration is enabled. elkIntegrationEnabled: true # logStashImage specifies the docker image containing logstash. # This parameter is ignored if &#39;elkIntegrationEnabled&#39; is false. logStashImage: &amp;quot;logstash:6.6.0&amp;quot; # elasticSearchHost specifies the hostname of where Elasticsearch is running.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publish logs to Elasticsearch</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.2.3/wccontent-domains/adminguide/weblogic-logging-exporter-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 16:43:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.2.3/wccontent-domains/adminguide/weblogic-logging-exporter-setup/</guid>
      <description>The WebLogic Logging Exporter adds a log event handler to WebLogic Server. WebLogic Server logs can be pushed to Elasticsearch in Kubernetes directly by using the Elasticsearch REST API. For more details, see to the WebLogic Logging Exporter project.
This sample shows you how to publish WebLogic Server logs to Elasticsearch and view them in Kibana. For publishing operator logs, see this sample.
Prerequisites This document assumes that you have already set up Elasticsearch and Kibana for logs collection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publish logs to Elasticsearch Using Fluentd</title>
      <link>/fmw-kubernetes/21.2.3/wccontent-domains/adminguide/logging-fluentd-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 16:43:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fmw-kubernetes/21.2.3/wccontent-domains/adminguide/logging-fluentd-setup/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This page describes to how to configure a WebLogic domain to use Fluentd to send log information to Elasticsearch. Here’s the general mechanism for how this works:
 fluentd runs as a separate container in the Administration Server and Managed Server pods The log files reside on a volume that is shared between the weblogic-server and fluentd containers fluentd tails the domain logs files and exports them to Elasticsearch A ConfigMap contains the filter and format rules for exporting log records.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>